Alright, what was I doing?
I think I was organizing some chests and shit.
With emphasis on shit, that is poop.
The thing that comes out of butts.
Hano is here.
What's up, Hano?
The only kind of wood I would bother dying is rich mohagony.
Dying any other wood is such a waste.
How dare you, sir?
Fuck your dive at.
Nobody wants that.
Also, look at this right here.
This is the ultimate dream of mine.
To have a perfect organizational setup.
And I don't like this butt following me around.
So I will actually get rid of it.
Okay, let's see here.
I want to continue finishing my organization.
I have some coffee here and I intend to relax today.
Oh yeah, that feels good.
Okay, so this chest right here, ores and ores, needs to be renamed.
Because this has now become accessories.
Wait, is that with 2s?
Accessories.
I think so?
I don't know.
Weapons.
Weapons is good.
Lawn mower could be considered a weapon.
But I don't know.
I feel like that is not a weapon.
Let's put it there.
Sort the items.
All of these are definitely weapons.
This right here?
No weapon.
This is a no weapon.
Accessories.
Put this in here.
Even though it's not really an accessory, is it?
It's more like a utility item.
What's that?
A butterfly.
Yonk.
Hold on.
Seabra swallowtail butterfly.
Did I just drop my...
Oh.
Interesting.
Okay.
Well, so here's the thing.
Organics are in these bamboo chests now.
Because bamboo is organic.
It makes sense.
I will be taking this seafood dinner with me.
The gold squirrel?
Let me test that with Dylan.
And I guess all the bait stuff.
Maybe we should have a fishing chest.
Think about that.
A fishing chest.
Fishing chest sounds good.
These are potions.
What are these?
I need to figure out how to make more types of chests.
Fast statue and magic mirror.
Always need to have it on me.
Glowsticks are good to have.
The money trough.
Hold on.
This thing is insane.
Can we agree on that?
That's actually wild.
The water gun?
I feel like that is the definition of a Michelinius item.
So maybe that goes in here.
Let's see here.
Gel is ammo.
We should have an ammo chest.
Potions.
Get out of there.
Let's sort this.
I guess I can remove one of these or sell one of them.
I don't need two of them.
It makes no sense.
This one also makes no sense to have.
Actually it does because you can craft with it.
Tattered cloth, lens, flare gun.
That's a utility item.
I feel like I should sell some of these.
These two can be sold.
The flare is ammo.
This can be sold as well because it sucks.
This is a helmet.
And this right here summons the blood moon.
What a horrible night to have a curse.
Bloody tear.
I guess I get these whenever I defeat a blood moon.
That would make sense.
I think I've had three, right?
Something like that.
The web rope can be sold because it's shit.
The chain though.
This one was a little interesting to me
because there were a bunch of recipes involving it.
And the book contains strange symbols.
Let's talk to Dylan.
Excuse me.
Where's Dylan?
Dylan?
What are you guys doing?
Um, crafting.
Tell me about the chain again.
Let's see.
Heart Lantern.
Steampunk chandelier.
Sawmill?
That one I have.
Li-sard chandelier.
Interesting.
You know what?
I should make a watch.
I should make a watch because sometimes
there's a shady dealer here
and he's like meet me behind the thingy
in three hours.
And I have no idea when three hours have passed
chest lock?
No.
A tin watch?
See, I can probably make that.
A chain and some tin bars.
I've got it, man.
If I remember where I put my tin bars.
Should be...
Is this...
Let's see here.
Where did I put those?
Oh, no.
Wait, wait a minute now.
It's not here.
This one...
Construction.
Where the heck did I put my...
Ah, there it is.
Okay, this needs to be renamed immediately.
Let's call this...
Ores.
And floors.
Not kidding.
Just ores.
Metals and shit.
You know all that.
Sorted.
Clayblog is construction.
So is that.
I guess that is as well.
This, that is as well.
I should have a gem chest.
Gems.
This one shall be gems.
Uh, open.
Oh, did I just...
Oh, no, not this one.
Uh, a chest.
Chests.
This is now gems.
And then...
Yoink.
Take all of these.
Sort.
Amethyst, topos.
Desert fossil.
Hmm.
The sturdy fossil.
Is this the same?
Oops, not restocked.
See, this one is differently colored,
so I feel like this doesn't belong here.
Maybe, honestly, maybe I should just...
organize the items based on the color
that the game already gives it.
Why make it more complicated for myself?
So right now, all of these are the same.
They're just ores.
All of them.
Even this one, I guess,
even though it's a tissue sample.
Why is it the same?
Hmm.
Oh, well.
Potions are here.
Let's sort.
Uh, our thingy here.
Bottles.
We have any other potions on me?
Hmm, doesn't look like it.
Golden key.
I'm curious about this purification powder.
Cleanses the evil.
I assume it is somewhat related to
what the dryad Rosalva is telling me.
A certain percentage of the world
is infected or something.
Let me see what she says again.
The sands of time are flowing.
And well, you are not aging very gracefully.
How fucking dare you?
6% crimson.
You have a lot of work to do.
Do I really, though?
6% is not a lot.
And it's not really moving either.
But I bet it will, at some point.
Okay then.
Give me that.
Did I put anything in these chests?
This was just for the looks.
I do kind of want...
You know what?
It would make more sense to have the
chest room at the bottom.
Just for easier access,
aka same thing I did in Minecraft.
But it's already up here, so.
It's probably okay.
Now, let's have a fishing chest.
This one can be fishing.
Fishing supplies.
That means bait.
And for now...
No, I'm not gonna keep this on me.
By the way, I was thinking.
Maybe I don't need to carry around
a million...
Like, I never use the bow, for example.
I can save a slot.
And I guess I can put the arrows in here as well.
But I guess I would need an ammo box.
That would make more sense.
What is this?
These are flags or banners.
Accessories.
Put the mining helmet in there.
Even though it's...
Yeah, it's okay.
Chains.
Put that in there.
I kind of want to sell some things.
I want to sell this and that.
Honestly, sell this as well.
One bomb.
Don't need one bomb.
Sell this one.
And...
That's good.
Let's open the gym.
Chest.
There.
Gems.
And put all our gems in here.
Now this dirty fossil.
Desert fossil.
I feel like that organics.
It's a fossil, right?
Even though I guess it's more like a stone at this point.
But yeah.
Bait, bait.
Wait, this technically counts as ammo, can I?
Oh.
That would be a spot to carry all the gel I find, actually.
You know what? Let's do that.
That makes a lot of sense.
Hey.
Fossils.
Feathers and seeds.
Sort all this.
I also want to sell these too.
Hanno.
Would you like these?
That's right.
Put the flare gun in here.
Along with the ammo for it.
Do I not have the ammo?
Grubby!
That's the Warcraft 3 pro player.
I love Grubby.
Let's put him in the gem's chest.
No. In the fishing chest.
Did I actually name the chest fishing?
I did.
There.
All of this goes in.
Didn't I have way more bait?
I'm losing my mind.
Here we go.
There. There we go.
I had more.
Did I not?
Topaz.
There you go.
Okay Dylan, real quick.
You need to tell me about this golden squirrel.
Stat.
Gold squirrel cage.
And a golden delight.
Major improvements to all stats.
Awesome!
With the gold.
Symbol there.
What does this require?
Cooking pot.
You know what?
Let's freaking do it.
Let's make that.
Crafting golden delight.
We got an achievement.
The Feast of Midas.
Obtain golden delight.
The highest quality meal
made from the highest quality ingredients.
I like it.
And that, my friends,
is the consumable I will be utilizing
when I fight very strong enemies.
Because I now have major boosts.
The book.
Remind me Dylan.
Why you?
I think Dylan is up to something with Hanno here.
I can make all kinds of bookcases, of course.
A piano?
So, here's the thing.
Some of these may have a function
that it doesn't tell you about.
So, I would have to think about this.
Like, is there any possible use for it?
So, a piano?
I don't know.
Maybe you can increase the happiness
among the people living here
or something with that.
But other than that,
I'm not entirely sure.
A meteorite piano?
Man, there is a lot of items in this game.
I mean, I want to make a bookcase, I guess.
Requires a sawmill.
Let's do it.
I just need some wood first.
Construction.
Give me the wood.
The sawmill is here.
Let's craft some bookcases.
Wait, is this not the sawmill?
Dylan?
Have you been lying to me?
Oh, wait, oh, wait, hold on.
Bone.
Oh, shit.
No, wait, this is not it.
Never mind.
Bookcase.
20 wood.
Ah, 10 books.
Fuck.
I don't have enough.
Oh, well.
That is unfortunate.
Potions.
Man, I need to learn where I put my things.
So potions is here, okay.
Didn't I put the stars in here?
Where did I put my stars?
Ah, here.
And the grenades.
You know what?
I'm going to sell those.
I'm going to...
Today is the day, by the way, where I will not die.
And I'm going to have an immaculate inventory.
Because now I also have a money trough.
A flying piggy bank to store my items.
Isn't that glorious?
Sandstone blocks.
Put all these in here.
Sort this.
Detonator.
All these statues, man.
Now this one goes not in here.
The living loom.
Let's actually put that somewhere.
Let's put it...
You know what?
Let's put it up next to Rosalva.
She would love that shit, right?
Oh, wait.
There's no room.
Rosalva!
I know you want this.
Maybe I can sneak it in here.
That works.
Not the best or prettiest, but it'll have to do for now.
Michelin, put this back in here.
A large explosion that will destroy most tiles.
Let me experiment with the dynamite.
Just a simple dynamite.
Now the flare.
Kind of needs to go in here for now.
I need to have an ammo chest.
Which one should it be?
I feel like I need to make a third row here.
Let's do it.
Let's not talk about it.
Let's just do it.
Whoops.
Wait, I forgot how to play this game.
How do I...
Oh, I can't because of the chests, of course.
Right, I can stand here.
It's obviously a shelf.
I'm so sorry.
You go in here.
Beautiful.
I'm gonna make this just a tad bit higher here
so I can have a third row of chests.
Now the question is though,
will I be able to reach it standing down here?
I need to test that.
So it would be...
There, let me remove one chest.
Put it here.
Oh, I can't reach it.
That's annoying.
But I guess I could just jump up.
It's not really the end of the world.
Can I though?
Put it one lower.
It doesn't seem like it.
I'm actually gonna make a third row.
Just for the future.
There we go.
Do-do-do-do-do.
And we're gonna make it like a very tight fit here.
There we go.
Oops, I kind of need to go back in again.
This is a good start.
I need the wall now.
Oh, but I need the other wall.
This wall.
Right.
Yeah, yeah, this is it.
This wall is correct.
Anything I missed?
Okay.
Beautiful.
And then we can fill that up later with more chests.
For now though, let's put a simple light in here.
Maybe I can put the light.
Actually, there's no room for light.
I should have a little bit of...
I can make a window, I guess.
That's gonna let in light, right?
That's gonna be for later.
What is in here?
The grenades.
Hano.
Usually take these.
Honestly, take this as well.
I've tried it before, I believe, with a detonator.
Everything's fine.
By the way, here's the thing I wonder.
It says medium improvements to all stats, and then 8 minutes.
This one says major improvements to all stats, 48 minutes.
I do wonder if the major and the medium just refers to the duration,
or if it actually means better stats.
I guess I gotta test that.
Now I have some worms here,
but I do want them on me because I'm gonna go fishing as well today.
I guess I don't need the dirt block.
Do I, though?
It's kind of nice to have on me.
Yeah, I'm gonna bring it.
The weather vane.
I'm gonna put that on our house.
Love that I can fly.
There we go.
Pretty.
A little bunny.
You come with me, and you go in organics.
Kind of funny.
The crimson rod is not that great.
I'm gonna put it in here and save myself a slot.
God damn it, you can't stop me.
I don't need two dinners.
These are ores.
These are gems.
Let's have these be food.
You know, food is good.
Speaking of food, I will save this for later.
Save it.
Now the gold.
Goes in the piggy bank.
How much do I have?
43?
How much did that minigun cost?
See more.
Dante.
I want what Catlin is selling.
What do you mean?
She doesn't sell anything?
46 gold.
We're almost there.
Probably I can sell him...
Is this really only 76 silver for all of these bullets?
That's not worth it.
I don't believe that for a second.
I guess I got to check these vendors as well regularly
because they sometimes have more items.
You know, these Ethereum goblins are nothing like my people.
Really rowdy bunch.
Not that my people are much better.
So the whole happiness system here is also intriguing to me.
They obviously prefer to live in different places.
So maybe I'll have to just check...
Maybe I'll have to write this down, actually.
Let me see here.
The crowding triggers bad memories of goblin war camps.
I really hate it.
Panel the die trader understands how fun it is to mix things together.
I can respect that.
So you don't like that it's crowded.
I guess you want to optimally live in a tree or something, right?
Far away from everybody like a hermit.
I get that.
Trust me.
I understand you.
Also, I wanted to reevaluate my choices here for accessories.
Now that I have them all collected here,
I kind of just want to take another look.
So I'm definitely wearing the crimson armor.
The precise shield of ketulu.
That's a must.
The rocket boots.
Is it though, actually?
I guess it is.
That's totally a must.
Increases movement speed and acceleration.
This one was very nice.
This one is insanely nice.
This one...
I don't know if it's nice.
I don't know if five armor penetration is a lot.
You know?
And I guess this would work better with fast weapons.
That deal less damage overall.
If you think about it, if you deal like a hundred damage per swing.
And only you get five extra damage penetrating armor.
Whereas if you have something that shoots fast,
it's gonna penetrate a lot more armor, right?
So I guess it depends on the weapon.
And then I have all of these.
This one is shit.
This one I can...
Actually, let me keep that.
This one I will sell.
Negate's fall damage.
This one is kind of cool, but I don't need it.
Useless for me right now.
The collection of vine rope from vines.
I don't think I need that either.
This one could be cool to experiment with.
In fact, yeah.
Here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna have a loadout 2 here.
Oh man, my loadout 2 is gonna be mega utility.
So I click a button and I can see rare creatures and shit.
So that means we also need a radar on that.
And what else?
Let me also put this up here.
That goes away.
Slowly regenerates life.
No.
Wait, this is the same, but better.
So I guess I can sell that.
It takes enemies around you plus 4% damage.
So this one is shit.
We can even take this.
And actually, let me have this instead.
These can be material though, so maybe I should keep them.
This one is not a material, so this one I can sell.
The bone rattles.
I don't know about that one.
That's weird.
This one is a material, so let's keep it.
This one though is the utility item for sure.
This is a vanity item.
Maybe I can hang that on the hat rack.
Make it look nice.
Okay, sort that.
Look at me right now.
I look like a construction worker.
I like it.
So here.
Oh, there's only room for two.
Crap cake.
Cakes made of poop.
And put it back in.
The rest here I will sell to Hano.
Excuse me, Hano.
Do you want a guy to plant fiber cordage?
Sure you do.
Man, I'm gonna have enough money for...
Ah, maybe not.
Never mind.
I thought I would have enough money for the minigun.
Quick stack.
Flies down there.
That's beautiful.
Okay.
So I have two quests right now.
I need to find a bunnyfish.
And I need to find a pengfish.
So, I'm gonna do that.
I'm gonna do that right now.
What were my keybinds for changing loadouts?
I have to remember this.
Loadout 1, 2, F3, F4, F5.
Okay.
Nice.
Beautiful.
And we even have this.
This is insanity.
I guess in this one I can put...
Hmm.
I guess all of these come in handy.
So, maybe this one goes in here for now.
Wait a minute.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, what?
Oh.
Wait, they are shared.
They're synced.
Oh!
I see.
So maybe it's better if I store my money somewhere else and not here.
Right?
Otherwise, this is taking up slots.
Uh, just...
Where can I store it?
I guess...
Actually, this is the valuables chest.
Yeah, let's put it in here.
So, we're gonna summon this guy again.
Take this.
Open this.
Put it in.
And now, when we look in the thingy here...
Perfect.
The golden key I will carry with me.
But not now.
Okay.
Let's go out and fuck some shit up.
Let's just go.
I should bring my little friendo.
In fact, I'm gonna put that friendo in the flying piggy bank.
Michelinius.
There we go.
Summon Abigail.
And now we're on the move.
Okay.
Oh man, I need to drink more of this coffee.
This is so good right now.
Oh, don't kill it.
I wanted to, you know...
I wanted to...
With my...
Didn't quite work out.
What's up, zombies?
How's it hanging?
Just get away from me.
I need to turn down this game just a tad.
Hold on.
There we go.
A bit too loud.
So what is my plan right now?
Um, I want to...
What was my plan last time when I went exploring?
I guess I want to find the bunnyfish.
Um, I wonder if this counts where I am right now.
Maybe I shouldn't do it during the night.
You know what?
This is a prime opportunity to go to the old man, I guess.
Since it's night and I want to teach him a lesson.
Probably he's going to teach us a lesson and that's fine.
It is a lesson I would like to have.
And that's fine.
Shoot up there.
Also, I should have brought some banners if I'm actually going to do this.
I'm not very optimal on my part there.
Oh, I have a nice little...
Oh right, this stuff.
That's right.
That's what I was doing.
I need to figure out what I can craft with that.
I remember this now.
What is this?
Oh, this is the banner for fighting these.
Wait a minute, where's my gun?
Oh, wait, I forgot my gun.
Oh, that's actually a major mistake.
Let's go back.
I need the gun.
Gun is mucho importante.
I'm dying here.
I'm burning.
Did I put the gun in here?
What is wrong with me?
Is that the one I had?
20, 5% speed, 10% speed.
Yeah, that seems about right.
Ruthless flaming mace.
Ah, this one is so 39.
It's a great weapon.
Where's this fucking badass thing I also had?
This one.
If I'm going to fight that guy,
I'm actually going to exchange...
Oh man, I don't want to exchange any of it.
The double jump is...
Let's exchange this.
If I can confuse a big enemy,
that's fucking amazing.
I don't know why I like killing bunnies.
I just do.
Oh, let me bring some banners as well.
So the old man.
What kind of banner would that be?
Banner banner.
Let's see.
Blood crawler, zombie face monster demon.
I guess a demon eye.
I guess it could be diabolical.
Could could be zombie, I guess.
Marching bones.
Give me.
Honestly, marching bones sound like it could be it.
I'm going to put all of them down.
Okay, let's get a move on.
Ah!
Yeah, that's how you catch them.
Maybe stupid eyes.
I need to mow the lawn here.
Like that.
We can just do it while we walk.
I guess mowing the lawn won't help me here though.
In this evil land.
In this crimson land.
That's such a weird effect that I can do this with it.
I wonder what the point is.
Just to determine when it comes back, I guess.
Maybe there's more that can be done there.
Love my gun.
Love it.
I want to find a better gun.
Well, I guess I can buy the minigun soon and experiment with that.
That's got to be my next gun.
But I want to find a sniper.
I want to find something high impact, long distance.
Lots of damage, goodness, basically.
That's what I'm after.
Oh, and we also needed to go to the icy region for the pinkfish.
The little brat sent us on a task.
I intend to fulfill that task.
Just, man, fighting on an incline like this looking down is horrible.
He's so dumb.
He keeps walking.
Oh, no.
Is it morning now?
Damn it, man.
That's okay.
We're going to go to the icy region and fish.
Yep.
We're fishing.
It's fishing time.
Give me that.
Mow the lawn everywhere.
Let me take a shortcut here.
Here we are.
Do we have a body of water here?
We do actually.
Perfect.
Winter wonderland.
I kind of want to go caving down here beneath the snow as well.
Maybe I'll do that after I find the pinkfish.
Okay, here we are.
Look at this weird-ass fishing pole.
I don't like how that looks.
That's scary.
Makes me uncomfortable.
It's an evil fishing pole.
Oh, that was too early, I think.
Am I actually having horns?
So I'm wearing the evil armor.
Atlantic card.
Isn't that interesting?
Come on.
Abigail, Abigail.
Ah, you're too slow, damn it.
You suck.
Abigail is kind of shit, honestly.
Can I get rid of her?
How do I get rid of you?
I'm not sure how to get rid of you.
Maybe I need to die or something.
That's probably a way.
Oh, please get away.
Fuck off.
Let me fish in peace.
I want- when you want to fish, you want to-
you want it peaceful.
Not all this fighting.
A frost dagger fish.
What's that?
Oh.
Well, okay.
Interesting.
Just throw a frozen fish at the enemies.
Sounds legit.
Frost Mino.
Come on, Abigail.
A crate.
I love getting crates.
Obsidian skin.
Immunity to lava.
That's fantastic.
Give me all this money.
Wait, is the projectile moving slower on the water?
It definitely is.
Look.
Cool effect.
Come on.
Kill it, Abigail!
What was that just now?
Damn, fuck these slimes.
This game is relentless with the enemies.
You don't get a moment's rest.
Iron crate.
Master bait.
And gravitation potion.
Fantastic.
Why does that do so little damage?
Okay.
No, it's master baiting.
It should be using the normal regular bait.
God damn it!
How can I make it-
Okay, I guess it doesn't matter.
That's fine.
Maybe I just put it-
Give me.
Oh, he is so quick.
Oh, I love getting crates so much.
A hard step stool!
That's fantastic.
Hold up to reach higher.
What?
Hold on.
What do you mean?
Hold up.
Are you for real?
I just bring a step stool with me.
That's hilarious.
I like that.
That's actually great.
Amazing.
Come on, pinkfish.
I need you.
Where's my fucking thing?
There it is.
Maybe I can convince him this is a pinkfish.
Maybe he's that gullible.
Look, I found you a pinkfish.
It was swimming in the pond.
Bro, this bait right here is immaculate.
I do wonder if there's a higher chance of getting something if you throw it far.
Let me fish.
Yeah.
Look at that pro MLG 360 no scope skill right there.
Crop rotation in effect.
Bro, this quest is insane.
Come on.
Why is this so difficult to find a goddamn pinkfish?
We're a bunnyfish.
I want it bad.
Man, give me the money.
Man, I look so high level.
I have the craziest gear right now.
As soon as night falls,
I'm going to go over there and punish an old man.
Ten mana potions and platinum.
I love getting crates in this game.
It's unreal how good that feels.
I absolutely love it.
I should make a...
I have an idea.
Even more.
Apprentice bait as well.
Man, I just keep getting bait.
What's that?
It's a balloon.
Abigail socks.
I'm not going to use her anymore.
Cobroar.
Okay, I'm going to give up on this for now.
Let's go in the cave.
Abigail, let's go.
We are due down below.
We need to do things.
And hold on.
I need to equip my...
thing there.
Let's do that.
And let's quickly get some air.
And then I'm going to sort my inventory.
I'm just going to go like this.
And I'm going to go deposit all and then take only a certain things.
Like the statue and shit.
Actually, these can stay in here for now.
I guess the axe of stuff is pretty nice to have.
Purification powder.
Holy shit, it's hot in here.
Hold on a sec.
I need to open the window.
Fuck, the window was already open.
You hate to see that.
Um, honestly, remove that.
Remove that.
And look at our clean inventory right now.
It's fantastic.
See you flying piggy bank.
See you later.
Give me these.
Just dig down.
Down, down, down, down.
Where you go?
I should make some air pockets down here.
What is that right there?
Oh, is that my glow stick?
Dig down, down, down, down, down, down.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Oh, here we go.
Beautiful.
Look at this.
Oh wait, didn't I get a...
Ah shit, I think I put that potion in my thingy.
Gotcha.
What's that?
Huh, there's a little thingy.
Make a little air pocket here.
Okay, it's time to drain.
Drain the shit out of this place.
Well, only to fill this up one up, I guess.
I've got some lads.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
This feels really good.
Make a little pocket there.
I guess there's technically a little moon pool.
Let me fill this up with water.
There we go.
What a weird cave system.
Oh yeah, here we go.
We're gonna drain so hard right now.
The ultimate drainage.
Oh yeah, baby.
Look at that.
Beautiful stuff.
What do we got down here?
Keep going down.
See, this is why I need a watch,
so I can see what time it is right now.
I need to know when it's time to go face the old
man.
He wants a piece of me and I'll gladly oblige.
Did I see something over there?
I think I see something on the right.
Something that's close.
What is that?
Ah, the little thingies.
Not mushrooms.
What are they called?
Jellyfish.
Man, mining is incredibly relaxing
because there's no enemies when you do it.
It's just... I get the same feeling in Minecraft.
It's just so nice.
I enjoy it.
The hell is this?
Oh, you want a piece of me?
I should really have a potion to breathe on the water.
Man, this cave is horrible.
Uh oh.
Am I okay?
Yeah, I get the...
Yeah.
Here we go.
Look at that.
What do we got here?
I'm taking the scenic route here.
Oh.
Holtz.
How do I...
How do I actually exit this properly?
Do I really have to right click that?
Oh yeah, baby.
Look at that.
300 HP.
I wonder what the limit is.
Bombs?
That's actually not too bad right now.
Thank you.
I'm scared of hazards in here.
I should have brought my hazard potion.
Man, this is a cave system, huh?
No enemies in here.
Not really.
What's that?
Oh.
What?
I found a money dimension.
Some sort of golden hole.
With riches.
That's fucking amazing.
That was so cool.
Okay, thank you.
Oh, we're in a different biome now.
Oh, it's dark in here.
This bomb right here?
I have 15 of them.
This is nice.
Let me replace the penguin.
Umbrella?
Maybe I shouldn't pick everything up I see, actually.
Now that I think about it.
Maybe I should prioritize.
Just ignore the things I don't need.
I feel like at this point in time,
I have a decent understanding of what I may need.
But it's always hard to know because,
you know,
you never know.
Ruthless wooden boomerang.
Oh, I have to try that one.
Let's put it here, I guess.
Builder potion, nice.
And coins.
Good stuff.
Wait, I've been here.
Oh, this is that...
Oh, it connects like that.
That's lovely.
What's up, bro?
Give me that lens.
Give me your cornea.
Okay, uh, what was that?
Interesting.
What do we got up here?
Nothing!
Oh, I see something.
What do we got down here?
More bombs.
Nice.
So let me try this.
It does exactly what I expected it to.
It's very slow, though.
But I guess it returns quick when you hit them.
Okay.
It's not bad.
It's just not very good,
compared to my other items.
Here's a question.
Let's say I do this now.
Open and I go...
Oh, that's beautiful.
Exactly what I need is.
Um, you know what?
These grenades right here.
Just throw them somewhere.
Oh, it doesn't even...
Right, because they're grenades, I guess.
Shrapnel.
I'm not going to destroy blocks.
I'm going to go down here now.
Let's go for a ride.
Want to go for a ride?
Bing, bing.
I feel like I should pick this
up and take it with me.
But I can just craft it, I guess.
Oh, what is this?
We just changed the biome again.
I guess we're in that...
Where are we right now?
I guess it's sort of a...
Not really a jungle
and not really a forest somewhere in between.
Shoot again.
I like destroying these little things.
Oh, man.
What is the deal with these?
Maybe I need something special
to break them open.
Um, can I really not place a thingy?
There we go.
Torch.
Man, I'm never going to run out of those.
Whoa, what a shot.
That was beautiful.
Okay, nothing up there.
See, I can't...
The funny thing is I can walk up there
but I can't come back.
It's a weird arrangement there.
That's a chest!
Hunt a potion.
Shock bait.
Oh.
Trident!
Increases...
Hold on.
We got to take care of these fools.
Increases mobility and water when held.
That seems pretty cool.
Hold up when descent.
Hold up to descent slower.
Oh.
Awesome.
Well, okay.
Let me put this in here.
Let's try it.
Are you going to do anything?
Let's just sit there.
I'm taking this chest with me.
This is...
This goes in my chest collection.
Let me try the trident.
Where'd it go?
Here.
Oh, what the...
Ice cream!
Eat it!
Quick!
Ah, get away.
Man, what is this weird ass biome here?
Look at the background.
Rope and silver.
Is this platinum?
No, it's lead.
It's fine.
I'm actually...
I'm going to make my way through here, actually.
You know what?
Bomb the shit out of that.
Beautiful.
Got to utilize those bombs.
We find so many of them anyway.
Just use them.
Just use them, damn it.
Hoi!
Oh, the skills.
Another line.
Oh, that was close.
You see that?
Fucking boulder fell from up top here.
I just saw my life flash before my eyes.
Scary stuff.
You.
I had the intention to collect you with my thingy,
but then I remembered you're evil.
We do not condone evil in this land.
Aha!
Enemies!
Foul beast.
Man, he got smacked.
I feel like I did a lot of damage to that guy.
Where are we going?
Oh, we've got some stuff down there.
Oh, it's this type of cave again.
Where have I seen this?
Here.
Maybe it connects, honestly.
Probably what's going on.
Nice.
Give me teal mushroom.
Oh, we've got some stuff up there and something in there.
Ooh, I'll hold on a second.
Corrupt statue.
All right.
I do wonder if they have any gameplay effect in any way.
They probably do.
Because there's so many of them.
So, it's got to do something.
What's my thinking here?
Um, nah, whatever.
Let me actually try this.
Whoa!
Okay.
Oh, that's a heart!
Hey!
Why isn't this doing shit?
What the fuck?
What's happening?
What is damaging me?
Oh, we can totally go more than 300.
Awesome!
This thing right here is pissing me off.
Fuck off.
Low stakes for everybody.
What's going on there?
Oh, wait, that's crimtane.
I know what that is.
Let's get it.
Blow that shit up.
Mmm!
Hell yeah.
Let's equip this.
Oh man, this is so good!
That's a sick utility item.
Oh, we made it.
Okay, I'm going to go down here now.
Shoot him out of the sky!
There's another heart!
Ooh, this cave is the tits!
What's that?
Oh, it's just some kind of thingy.
Thank you.
Amazing.
This expedition so far has been incredible.
And all of this extra HP is surely going to help us
against the old man and his antics.
He's most definitely an evil entity and he needs to be dealt with swiftly.
But we cannot let our guard down.
We got to respect the old man.
Oh, that's a trap!
Hold on now.
Fuck off, trap.
Let me remove it.
The hook?
Hmm.
I guess I'll keep that.
Silt and mud can go away.
Let me quickly do this then.
And quick stack.
Not that as much as stack, but you know.
Old fish.
Oh shit!
I was about to die.
Let's bomb the shit out of this place.
So satisfying!
Not that I needed to do any of that actually.
Um, where should I go?
This definitely connects to this over here.
This is one big crazy cave.
And I love it.
What just damaged me?
Oh wait, is it the stuff falling?
Falling blocks maybe.
That's probably what that is.
I need to make scarab bombs.
Those are incredible.
I wonder if I can make them right here.
I can make, oh I can make sticky bombs right here.
That's nice.
You know what, why not?
They're way better, mostly.
Ah, we got some gems.
Emeralds, beautiful.
An evil bat.
Let me actually go up first.
There's nothing up here.
I don't know.
What the fuck?
There's a tree here.
Huh?
Isn't that interesting?
I feel like that's very interesting.
Delete that and that.
What is, I'm gonna bring that home I guess.
Cobweb fuck off.
Glink roots.
Oh, almost dropped it.
Here's what I want to do now.
I'm gonna try and fish here.
Come on Abigail, kill it.
50th cave bat.
Oh, there's a heart down there too.
Cool.
Come on now.
What is hiding down here in these murky waters?
Maybe nothing.
Give me that.
Oh my god, we have been upgraded so hard.
Lovely.
Now I want to go over here I guess.
Because why not?
I see a little pot that needs to be broken.
Let's go this way.
Actually.
Make a hole through this whole thing.
Why you may ask?
It's simple.
It's satisfying.
Oh yeah, look at that.
Feels good, yo.
Glow sticks.
Just throw them around.
I wonder if they last forever.
They probably do, right?
What's that?
Oh, it looked like a little treasure thingy.
Got a salamander.
Let's see if we can surprise him here a little bit.
A salamander.
That's for you.
Salamander.
Ah, he's going to walk away.
I don't see anything.
Oh, I see a little room there.
That's intriguing me.
What's that?
A crawdad.
Okay, nice.
Oh, what's happening?
What's that?
What's this?
A campfire?
Sure, let's put it back.
Nice to have a campfire here.
Let's up the spirits a little bit.
Ah, we can't throw that far.
I wonder if this is faster than just mining.
When you do it one by, I think it is.
But just barely.
It's a bit of a pain to mine upwards in this game.
Um, what do I see?
Let me actually zoom.
Okay.
Um, let me go in here.
Looks a little bit intriguing.
Thank you.
More bombs.
Always lovely.
Ah, damn it.
Hop, hop, hop, hop.
Motherfucker.
Man, I am bombing the shit out of everything here.
Got caught in the blast.
You love to see it.
Ooh, that, that hurt.
Oh, oh, let's be careful here.
Dangerous terrain.
Let's just heal.
Ah, I see some crimtane.
Let's go over here.
What's that?
Pressure plate.
Uh, boom.
Nobody likes pressure plates.
Boo.
Nobody likes silk blocks.
I do want this yellow stuff, though.
Topaz.
Yeah.
Man, imagine having the shitty pig axe right here.
This is the good one and it feels slow.
But wait, didn't I get a thingy?
Hold on now.
Sort the inventory.
Uh, boom.
Hunter builder.
Hold on.
In here.
Sort, did I bring a potion in here?
Lesser healing.
I thought I had one of those-
I thought I had one of those mining faster potions, but I don't.
Feels good to uncover all of these cave networks, though.
Little by little, um, I want to go left.
Heh. Nice choke point there.
You there.
That's a black slime!
I don't know if I've seen those before.
Must be a rare one down here.
Gimme all the gems.
Thank you.
Oh, I thought that was a chest.
Oh! Mika!
I'd lend you a hand, but last time I did that, I didn't get it back for a month.
Oh, I see. Uh...
Uh, okay.
Purple counterweight. Those are counterweight after hitting an enemy with a yo-yo.
I mean, vine rope?
Strange brew?
Unpredictable healing, inconsistent potion sickness, brief periods of inexplicable invulnerability.
It looks and smells terrible.
I'll have five.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mika.
You are the grandest in all the land.
I want this.
And I want this. Ah, do I really want to go up there just for that?
Let's see here.
Oh, I see a heart!
Heh heh heh!
Maybe I should play zoomed out for a bit.
It is definitely... you have an advantage for sure when you do it.
It's just so much more comfortable to play zoomed in.
At least not all the way, but somewhat, you know?
Man, I love the flying that I can do here.
What's that sound?
Oh, I don't have any room.
Even with this, I'm like...
Completely full here. What is that?
Cave bat banner. Oh, okay.
Corrupt statue. Let's do that shit.
Water chest.
I guess...
Silt lock. Fuck off.
What is that?
Granite elemental!
Hold on now!
Oh.
No. Don't fish it!
It dropped spaghetti.
This game makes so much sense.
Major improvements to all stats for 8 minutes.
Okay, so major definitely means you get better stats.
It's not just a duration for sure.
I mean, I pretty much knew that.
But it's good to have it confirmed.
There's another heart on my gracious meat.
Look at that. 400 HP.
I feel like this is so neatly stacked, there's no way I can get more.
This has to be the limit.
There's a statue here of somebody.
Goblin.
I wonder if I place that next to...
What was that?
Oh, it was a trap.
Righto.
Rid of that.
Okay, let me get rid of these traps.
It's just good practice. Get rid of it.
There's something above me as well, actually.
Let me quickly check that out.
That's a button!
Sort.
Remove the dark traps.
The silk blocks and the mud blocks.
And I guess the snow blocks and the...
Hmm.
The granite block.
On the elemental.
There's something blue over there.
Man, this has been an exceptional cave adventure.
What's that?
I think it's time to go back, honestly.
Water walking potion. Not bad.
Not bad.
Get rid of that.
I'm going to go on for just a bit more here.
It's too addicting. I want to keep going.
You know how it is.
Let's quickly open the thingy.
No!
Shit.
Okay, it's back. We're fine.
Quick stack.
Slush block.
Heart reach.
Increases pickup range for life hearts.
I mean, sure.
Just use that.
Doesn't seem terribly useful, honestly.
Extremely situational and...
I don't know, just not that great, I guess.
But look at that on the left. That guy has a caving helmet.
I see him.
Nah, fuck that guy.
What's over here now?
Oh, I think we're entering back into the...
the icy domain.
Sort of.
Not quite, but soon.
More bombs. Lovely.
Mushroom torch.
I will take these.
What's that over there?
Ah, just more of them.
What's that?
Cockneel beetle.
I want to find more chests.
Also, I think we may have enough gold right now for...
Hold on, hold on a minute. What's this?
Granite!
Let's collect a bunch.
This is new to me.
In fact, let's bomb the shit out of it.
That's how we do it.
It's as simple as that.
Nice.
This place is huge.
Oh, that's a door!
Okay.
Oh, I don't have any room for shit right now.
Yikes.
Quick stack.
Gold? Oh, yeah.
Torch. Hunter.
Oh, shit, really?
I'll leave this.
This one I'll take, though.
Let's get rid of this.
I do want to bring this chest.
Wait, I can't?
Oh, because something is in it?
Let's, um...
Let's do this!
Fire in the hole!
Ho-ho!
Chest still stands.
Strange, strange, that fellow?
Why can't I remove it?
Oh, shit. There we go.
Oh, it's like, uh...
Immune while it's in that state.
Huh.
That chest is...
Coming with me.
Oh, it's because I don't have any room.
Ah, of course.
Jay Parker III.
Sure.
Uh, let's get rid of that.
Get that door.
Is that...
Is that another door I just got?
It's so dark here!
Oh!
Granite Golem!
Looked like he had a lot of HP there.
I didn't quite get to see it in time.
Let me call potion, sure.
Wait, don't I already have?
Bro, this is exciting.
It's time to go back though.
Because my shit is full.
Just use the potion.
Uh, get rid of that.
Let's... wait, what?
Oh, no.
Fuck, I thought that was the recall potion.
I'm an idiot.
Just use that.
Here we go.
Exciting stuff now, because we have...
A lot of money.
So I know what I'm doing.
Dante!
I come...
to you with money.
He sells illegal gun parts now!
And unholy arrows.
So I would like to purchase this mini-shark.
Oh wait, I don't have the money on me.
Wait.
Hold on.
Ah, okay, perfect.
Wait.
I have 68 gold now.
Holy crap.
Mini-shark time.
Completely awesome!
Obtain a mini-shark.
That's me, I have it.
Let this one better be...
Fantastic.
It's probably eating bullets like crazy though.
Oh, yeah.
Boy, oh boy.
Boom, boom, boom.
Okay, so Dylan.
There was something I could use the mini-shark for
and upgrade it with.
And mega-shark.
Oh, but I need soul of might and I have no idea how to get that.
Star cannon, meteorite bar and fallen star.
We can... wait a minute.
Oh, it shoots fallen stars.
Holy shit.
That's gonna be...
expensive ammo.
Woo!
I mean...
I'm tempted.
No, I'm gonna wait a bit.
I'll wait a bit because if I turn it into that,
I can't use it in the normal fashion, right?
So, yeah.
I don't know, dude.
We're gonna wait.
A ruby!
That's new.
In fact, Dylan.
Dylan.
How about this ruby?
What can I make?
A ruby.
A crown.
I kind of want to try being...
a mage.
There's definitely, like, look at this.
Reduced mana cost and there's definitely, like,
mage outfits and gear and shit.
But then again,
I kind of want to just shoot things.
In fact, that's more appealing to me right now.
Yeah, I want to shoot people.
Tell me about this...
slush block.
Oh, you don't do anything with that, huh?
So it's like crap.
I don't want to place it either.
How about this hard step stool?
Hand of creation?
Holy shit, that's a lot.
Bro, I don't have any of this.
Okay, I'm definitely saving the step stool.
Seems to come in good use later on.
Now granite doors.
That's construction.
Strange that fellows.
Uh...
There's some strange dead fellows in there.
Now the hook.
What are the other uses for this?
Where's the hook?
Okay, just a grappling hook, so it's not really...
that useful.
In fact, you can have it.
You can have these as well.
I don't like it. Actually...
Yeah, keep them.
Let's see. The water chest?
Let's put that there instead.
This is like the specialized item. This is valuable and this is...
to be determined.
He's thinking about spiders. I don't like Hano.
Hano alert! Hano alert!
Granite chest.
You know what? That makes sense for the oars.
That's going to be the oar chest.
No, place it right next to it, though.
There.
Cave bat banner.
I doubt we're going to see cave bats up here and do we really need a banner for cave bats?
I mean, if you're having trouble with cave bats...
I think that's bats.
What do you say?
Granite blocks, though.
Some material, so Dylan, will you take a look at this thing I found here?
I can smooth it out. Why?
Why would I do that?
Why would I smooth the granite?
Make it look nice, maybe.
Workbench.
Mana potion.
Oh.
Mana flower.
Automatically use mana potions when needed.
Oh, that's kind of cool.
Seems like some mage shit that I don't need right now.
I would like some spaghetti, though.
Not going to lie.
Potions.
Let's put this in here.
Man, I have a ton of lesser healing.
So that means...
we need to grab...
Where are they?
Are they on me?
These ones.
Glowing mushrooms.
And then we need this.
Wait, is that the one we need?
Bottle?
You should see if I remember.
Yes, sir!
Beautiful.
I do remember that.
Hundred, though.
It's not really that much anymore, is it?
Now that we have 400 HP.
There's got to be a way to make even better ones.
Let me think.
Builder potion.
Master bait.
Actually, I'm going to...
Can I keep this for now?
What's in here?
Tiggle.
No, don't throw it.
And then do that.
Oh, it actually... okay, interesting.
Diabolic sigil.
I do want to keep that because it's time.
Marching bone, I'm going to bring that.
The cot!
In here.
Man, I have chests in here. Why do I have chests in there?
That makes no sense.
The seeds.
Bling root, wait a minute.
Hmm, what's that?
Whoop.
Grasshopper.
Huh.
Bait.
A bird.
It's just a bird.
What can I do with a bird?
Dylan.
Check out this burp.
I can make a bird cage.
I mean, sure.
Let's just cook it.
Cook that too.
This is the food one.
Copper ore that's in here.
Seeds.
There.
Whew, man.
Trident.
This one is very useful.
Let's eat that.
Man, it takes a while to do the inventory management in this game.
Whew.
Okay.
Um, let's figure out how to make a watch right now.
Fuck, what do I need for that?
See, this is the issue.
If I don't know where to start, it's the pain.
Let's see, lead.
Right, we have meteorite stuff.
I'm going to try that, actually.
Um...
Let's see here.
Yeah, it's not really that great.
Remind me what I can do with this?
Meteor, meteor.
Meteor.
Right, all these lightsabers.
Meteor staff.
Oof.
That seems crazy.
If that works, just like the blood and it does 56 per tick.
That's insane.
Wow.
Story cannon. This one, man.
This would be the gun to have if you really wanted to go to town
and punish someone in particular, you know.
I actually want to try something.
Audio.
To know audio.
General.
Let me try turning music off completely because there's actually constant music in this game.
And listen.
There's actually ambient sounds that I've never heard because the music is just constant.
So I'm gonna take a break here for my brain
and listen to no music for a second.
The golden key.
One locked gold chest or lockbox.
I'm assuming that's gonna be in the vicinity of the old man.
I feel like I can relax right now.
This is pure bliss.
Okay.
What was I doing?
Sticky glow stick.
I think I just want to go again.
Right now, in fact.
Oh, wait, let's leave this here.
Meteorite bar goes in.
Hold on, let me talk to this fucking brat over here.
I've had enough of you. Where are you?
Wait, who is it?
Hanno?
Are there three people up here?
Fjällr...
Oh yeah, he's sitting right there. Fucking hell.
Easy ones you as the official the robust can errant monkey.
What is it?
I finally found a jungle cat that likes water.
I think it's because it's also part fish.
I don't know why this happened and I don't want to know.
I just want it in my hands and make it snappy.
Let me guess.
Catfish?
Okay.
Easy.
Catfish.
We shall find the catfish.
Jungle, huh?
I think that's jungle.
We need jungle, I'm afraid.
Let's go to the jungle.
Man, there's actually no sounds when you walk around.
Maybe that's why there's music all the time.
This is oddly similar to Minecraft where there's just no sounds.
It's time.
We're gonna speed run over there.
Nope, not interested in your wares.
Man, these rocket boots right here.
I'm digging them a lot.
Look how fast I am.
Whoo-hoo.
Here we go.
This has to be jungle.
Don't you even think about it?
Okay, fine.
We have our master bait on as well.
This should be it.
Iron crate.
Calming potion, healing potions, and a weak falcon blade.
Ha!
Alright, I'm gonna try that later.
Interesting stuff.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah, right!
Okay, it's shooting fast.
Using lots of bullets.
I need to think on this weapon.
Oh, it's night. It's gonna be horrible to fish.
Fucking shoot him down!
Oh, it's really fun. This weapon is really fun.
Another crate.
Copper bar.
My god, man.
Let me fish in peace for fuck's sake!
This is so frustrating!
Like, I can't have five seconds!
Wow, that's doing a lot of damage.
Abigail is kind of...
Fuck off.
Base.
Maybe they can't get up to me here, actually, if they come from the left.
Another base.
What is happening here?
I should make a little... I have an idea, actually. I have an idea.
I can't believe I didn't think about this earlier.
It's time to fish in peace, goddammit.
This is how we do it.
And you know what? Stop making noise.
Okay, here we go.
Show me the catfish.
Crate.
Journeyman bait. Cool.
A quick falcon blade.
Jesus, what is it with these falcon blades?
Thank you.
Man, so many crates here.
Look at all these mo... oh, this is the perfect solution for this.
Just wall yourself off. That's got to be my go-to from now on.
A golden one.
You know what? I'm going to collect a bunch of crates and open them all at the same time.
That's going to be fun.
We wait, we wait.
I can actually look at the map while I fish.
Oh, you know what, actually?
This could also be jungle, actually.
Hold on. That looks... now I'm confused.
Shoot these guys down.
Hold on.
Oh, my...
See you later, suckers.
Let's get ready to make a fishing extraordinary hot.
Oh, actually, I should be utilizing this some more.
You can gain some speed like that.
Look at this.
While you're in the air.
Not bad.
I mean, this gun is really fun.
See, this could be jungle, actually.
Bamboo and shit, right? That's jungly.
Oh, my God. Fuck off.
There we go. Now we can fish in peace.
There we go.
I got to get rid of Abigail. She is annoying AF.
The sounds in my ear. I'm going to go...
Insane.
Oh, wait. Maybe this is not... oh, shit.
Is this not good enough water?
Fuck, I didn't even think about that. Hold on.
This may not actually be deep enough.
Maybe I have to go over here.
God damn it.
This has to be enough. There's a fish in here, damn it.
Shoot it out of the sky.
Why can't I...
Okay, good enough.
Let's try this.
Come on.
It's got to work.
Come on, come on, come on.
Is it because I'm technically making a smaller pool here?
I'm losing my mind.
Oh, I think it is.
Rip my... wait, why can't I get anything right now?
Tin can.
Catfish! Hallelujah!
Finally, I did it!
Fantastic.
Caught in jungle service.
Awesome. Okay.
Okay. Where are you at, you piece of shit?
You're up there.
Yeah.
Whoa, you actually did what I asked and survived.
Nice. Hand it over and beat it.
How about... okay, fine.
You're done. The grand easy dismisses you.
Bro, I'm about to evict your ass.
What did I get from that? Did I get some money?
I did not pay attention. Fuck.
Wait, can I see the chat log?
Servant and training.
Can I see my latest achievements somehow?
Can I click on this? Ah.
Complete your first quest for the angler.
Nice. Okay, well, there it is.
I finally did it.
Now I just need to find a bunnyfish and a pinkfish as well.
Quick stack. Put it all in.
Now this one. 27.
Let's see how fast it is.
I mean, not bad. Kind of weak range there.
It's pretty fast though, but it says very slow speed.
That's so interesting to me.
A weather raid? What?
What do you mean?
Clear. 10 miles per hour east.
Huh. All right.
We got some goodies.
Hold on, put this back.
1010 is trash.
Would you like a shitty falcon blade?
This one...
Yeah, fuck this. I hate Abigail.
Abigail, you're dismissed. You're gone.
Get the fuck away from me.
Put this in here.
Ah, the birds are chirping.
Calming potion.
Brother, I feel like that is going to be my bread and butter.
I absolutely love the idea behind that potion.
Let's grab the healing potions.
Let's grab regeneration.
Swiftness. Iron skin.
Mining. Actually, just one.
This one. Because here's the plan now.
Here's the plan.
Take one of these.
All right, this one. This one is kind of useless, I guess.
For me.
Immunity to lava.
That's good enough for now.
Sort.
Can I lock these?
I wish I could lock some of these slots so that when I sort, they get ignored by the sorting.
If you know what I mean.
Hold on. Maybe there is an option for that.
Controls.
Let's see here.
Smart cursor.
Hot bar.
Throw.
Auto select.
What's this? Menu controls. Wait.
Okay.
Hold on.
Interface.
Oh, hold on a second.
Classic.
Yeah, just...
Fancy is fine.
Hover text boxes.
General.
Smart doors. Oh.
Activate set bonuses.
Hover controls. Hold.
Interesting.
Well, well, well.
I do believe. So here's my plan right now.
I'm gonna go back into that cave.
On the left.
And when I get there, I'm gonna turn on music again, actually.
But I'm gonna go there. Wait for nightfall.
That's why I brought all this shit as well.
And then when night hits,
I'm gonna...
I can actually tell if it's night.
I wonder if this background will change when it's night.
I didn't quite pay attention to that.
Then I'm gonna go to the old man.
Oh, fuck. I actually brought all my money.
Maybe this is good in here, actually.
There we go.
That way, I won't lose it when I die.
You know, I could go down here.
No, but I actually...
I want to go to this part right here.
This special part right there.
That is an intriguing place.
Also, did I forget my...
I wanted to try the armor penetration with this weapon.
You know what? Let's go back.
I want to try that with this, because otherwise,
this one right here,
it doesn't seem that great.
Uh...
This one.
Let's try that.
Let's replace it with...
I guess that one for now.
Put this here.
I guess I should bring some of these.
Sure.
Why not? Put that there.
And then we switch gear.
Let me try this.
On the enemies.
Oh, it's still here. That's funny.
Okay, let's turn on the music again.
Let's put it at like...
I feel like that did more damage.
I don't know if all enemies have armor, though.
This one has 80 HP. Let's see.
Like 14, 12, 16-ish per shot.
Wait.
Six range damage.
Let's take this off.
And see.
I need a slime to test.
No more slimes when you need them, huh?
Not yet.
Fuck it. Put it on again.
I mean...
I feel like it's not as great
as I hoped it would be.
So I think I may turn it into
the star cannon thingy.
It also uses way more ammo.
Not that it really matters to have a shit ton of ammo.
Oh, I get it now. This is why it does way more damage
because I have nine here, so nine plus six, right?
It's definitely easier to shoot things out of the sky.
You don't have to aim as much.
A bit more forgiving in that regard.
Wait, what?
Unconscious man.
Ha! How did I get here?
The last thing I remember was a portal opening up
in front of me.
Hold on a second.
I've got enemies coming in.
Fuck off.
Eternia crystal?
For starters, take a few of these defender medals
on the house.
I've got some special defenses you can purchase
but only with defender medals.
Okay.
Just give me something.
Currency for trading with the tavern keep.
Rosalva seems nice. I should bring her back with me.
What?
We haven't even met her yet.
What do you mean bring her back?
What do you sell?
Lightning aura rod.
Summons a sentry.
Hold on a second now.
Ale.
Place in the Eternia crystal stand
to summon aetherious portals.
Oh, so I need this?
Interact
while carrying an Eternia crystal to summon
aetherious portals.
Hold on.
Fuck out of here.
I mean, I guess you're gonna go to my
place, right?
I can actually buy some of this.
Hold on. Lightning aura.
Uses summons a sentry.
A trap that explodes
when enemies come near.
Costs 10 aetherian mana per use.
What?
I have no idea
what any of this means.
Defenders forge?
Can be used to store your items.
Stored items can only be accessed by you.
50 though.
I mean, I'll try and buy this.
Sure.
I guess I'll see you around, huh?
Let me put that in here.
Oops.
That as well.
Why did I bring all of these?
That's so stupid.
Why did I bring that?
God damn it.
All right.
See you around, man.
I guess I'll have to make a room for you.
Actually, hold on. Before we...
I want to try something here.
If you're still hanging.
Oh, he's walking. Look.
You can see him on the map.
He's walking to town.
Sir?
Happiness.
I might want to get back to my place
in case anyone needs a drink or two.
Is this another invasion?
Oh, it's just the crimson.
Even worse.
Hate to say it, but I rather hate overcrowded quarters.
More tall, the demolitionist
is one crazy little drinker.
I love it.
Hold on a second. Motherfucker.
I like Fjäll the Goblin Tinkerer.
It shows you cannot always judge a person
by their origins.
Handle the Diet Traders eccentric and narcissistic personality
really makes me want to smash a table.
So here's what I think.
I think...
you should
quarter them with the people they like.
In the areas they like.
So it's kind of a puzzle.
It's kind of a puzzle you need to figure out here.
Who likes who?
Where they want to live.
And just keep all that in mind
and maybe something will happen.
I mean, what will happen if they're mad?
Maybe they'll leave, actually.
None of them have left yet.
So...
No clue.
Also, did I just notice the sun going down?
It became a little darker, didn't it?
For a second there.
What's that?
Shark pup.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
So weird.
Also, I passed the...
Oh yeah, this is a...
Big ass cave.
I feel like maybe if I go down there
I won't have time to get back up again.
Maybe I'll just wait.
Until night.
Maybe I can hang out
in some caves near the surface somewhere.
In fact, let me go a bit more left
of the old man.
Check more out what's going on there.
50th ice...
slime.
Very awkward to have to double tap the key.
I will not be very good at that.
I can tell you that much.
I'll be there yet.
Hmm.
Oh!
Water just became red.
Come on.
Can I do this here?
Wait.
Okay.
So it's...
It's fixed now.
I have cleansed the land.
What was that just now?
There's a weird sh-sh-sh effect
when I walk into this.
I don't think it's just the damage.
Maybe it is, actually.
Okay, the minigun is pretty decent.
Yeah, it's not bad.
It's actually comparable
to what I had before, at the very least.
I think it's getting... I think it's becoming night
right now.
This is not normal day lighting.
I feel like this is...
It's time!
Okay.
Ah, here we are.
This whole thing has become a jungle.
Okay, I think it's time.
Oh, you know what? I have an idea.
Ooh, no, wait, that's a bad idea.
We're going to place some of these.
We're also going to put some torches
to have some light.
Fuck off.
Let's close this door.
Then I need a campfire.
Best statue.
Uh, yeah, sure. Just put this here as well.
Why not?
Maybe a slime will appear in the middle of combat.
Oh, no, did I not bring my spaghetti?
Crap.
Drink this. Drink that.
That one.
This one.
I think we're about ready.
Lots of healing potions.
Lasagna.
Very good.
Quick stack.
Put that in there as well.
Let's try this.
Probably we're going to get our asses kicked.
I actually kind of forgot how this went.
Uh...
Sir?
Defeat my master and I will grant you passage into the dungeon.
Okay, sure.
Curse.
Oh, here we go. Here we go.
Fucking shoot him out of the sky.
Okay, we got a...
Ah!
I'm flying.
We're flying away from him.
Why can't I shoot?
Okay, okay.
I can't get past him.
Oh, he's taking very little damage.
Maybe he should hit his hands or something.
Hold on.
Maybe this weapon sucks? I'm not sure.
Oh, man. He takes very little damage.
Holy shit.
Yeah, I'm getting fucked here.
How do I... Ah, get away from him.
Get in here.
Fly!
We got a heal.
Okay, we healed.
Man, his reach is...
Dude, he's taking no damage at all!
Are you kidding?
Oh, look, his hands.
I think I need to... Yeah, destroy the hands.
That way he can't damage me.
Fuck his hands up.
Ah, shit. I'm just trying to tank this right now.
It's not going very well for me.
Fly!
Ah!
We need to heal real bad.
Shoot his hands!
Hands are soon gone.
Come on.
Get the hand.
Ah! I can't get around him.
Fuck!
Okay.
Mmm.
Got my ass kicked there.
But I think I understand what I need to do.
I need to take care of those hands.
The hands, man.
Oh, I'm all the way back here.
Let me actually see if I can get some better weapons.
Oh, look how nicely these glow.
During the night.
Dude, I feel so slow without...
Without that.
This one is incredible.
I need that.
Let's see here.
I don't think I want...
So what is this doing?
A chance to create illusions and dodge an attack.
Temporarily increases critical chance.
I mean...
It's hard for me to tell how good this is
because I don't notice this fucking shit during combat.
Maybe it does...
Something for me, but I have no idea
of knowing how good it is.
It's a crap shoot for me in the dark.
I feel like the flight is pretty essential.
Let's...
Replace that.
And utilize the other weapon.
Let's see here.
Where is it?
Actually, hold on. Let me see here.
Is there anything...
Anything...
This one...
Could be...
This one, actually.
I'm gonna bring that as well.
And...
What else?
This one is actually pretty cool.
But it's not fantastic.
Do we need to bring any other potions?
Wait, what?
What?
Oh, it's this one.
A strange brew?
Oh, actually.
I have an idea.
I have a great idea.
Here.
Mana potion.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm gonna perform a...
Look how fast we are now.
The power of this thing right here.
Fleeting magi luminescence.
Yes, indeed.
Let me chest the other weapon real quick.
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
I just want to see a quick comparison here.
I guess the...
Did I hear him over here?
There he is.
Let me quickly see the damage.
Okay.
I think, realistically,
in combat,
his arms are moving around so much,
I think I will have higher DPS
with the mini shark.
Simply because I...
I'm gonna have trouble hitting his arms,
shooting so slowly.
Even though it may, you know,
technically be higher DPS,
I think I will perform worse
with the undertaker.
Now, the harpoon
could be very nice in theory,
but it requires me to be very close.
I could practice a bit with it, I guess.
Yeah, it's very...
It's difficult.
Also, I gotta hurry before the night is over.
I need to actually sprint.
I need to make a minecart track, man,
to get back.
I wonder how long that's gonna take.
Like 76 crit,
that's insane damage.
Maybe this weapon
is the best to use.
Yeah.
Maybe when he's close, I'm gonna do this.
When he's far away, I do that.
That's the deal.
Oh no, it's morning!
Fuck!
I'm not gonna be able to
try him again.
Oh well, I guess it's time to go in this cave then.
We go back here.
Okay, hold on.
Nah!
Probably easier to craft.
Actually, wait a minute.
Yeah, I wanna go to the right.
I wanna go back down there.
Whew, man!
We got some speed!
Speed!
Hot damn.
Whoa!
That acceleration though.
Oh, brake!
The other way.
Let's get off.
Yep!
Let's see.
Left, sort of.
Let me go through here.
And then all the way down here.
And now we're back.
This is where I was.
What is all this?
Very nice.
Ooh, this goes deep.
Here we go.
Now we're sort of out of this area though.
Oh wait, there's more down here.
No, that's...
That's not the same area though.
Shoot the crabs!
Smash the crabs!
The crawdats.
Oh.
Wait a minute.
Did this statue just spawn?
A crab?
Oh!
Is that what it does?
No fucking way.
I get it.
I knew there was something about those stupid statues.
I guess you could...
Oh, so I guess why you would take them with you is...
Some enemies drop certain things.
So maybe you can always spawn one on command, I guess.
If you want to farm some of them.
Is that it? That's...
No wait, there's more on the right here.
Mother slime.
Is that it?
Is that all you got?
Let's blow this place to smithereens.
I love that.
Actually, let me go in the cave on the left.
I don't know why I'm doing this.
It makes no...
I should bring a watch!
But to do that...
I need to figure out how to make a watch!
Oh!
There we go.
That looks dangerous.
What do we got?
Oh, he's...
That's...
Okay, so 4 and 7? Hold on.
He looks armored to me.
Oh shit.
Oh yeah, that's helping a lot.
That is actually significant.
That's pretty neat.
Oops.
Okay, um...
Give me this.
That's a cool little effect.
How it lights up the cave.
When you use those rockets.
Oh, traps!
I don't know why I need to throw 3.
But, okay.
Oh, damn trap.
Nice lighting effects.
Oh, here we go!
Should I do that or not?
Come on, I don't know, dude.
That seems a little...
scary to me.
I do a lot of damage with this unpleasant meatball.
It is actually an...
ungodly amount of damage.
Oh!
That damaged me a lot just now.
I'm gonna be careful.
So...
Looks like we sort of cleared this cave.
There's also a little bit over there.
Maybe I'll check that out real quick.
And then it's time to head upstairs again.
I think it's soon time.
For the night.
And round 2.
Something up there it seems.
Oh, here we go.
Ah! Come here!
Ah, you fucker.
That looks like a dead end.
Looks like we explored this little area.
What is that sound?
What is that right there?
Oh, it's a hole!
I thought it was some sort of banner.
I'm getting good at moving through these caves though.
Better than I was, that's for sure.
I'm gonna head out again.
I wonder if it's night.
Let me check the map.
I don't think you can see whether or not it's night.
Actually, you know what?
Maybe there's more of those floating islands up there.
I have gravity potions.
I could also explore that if it's not night yet.
How long does that shit last anyway?
Quick stack.
And...
What else can I throw away?
Okay...
Okay, that's fine.
Don't go that way, don't go that way.
Look at this cave here.
This looks interesting.
It's a very weird background there.
Where am I going?
Okay, I'm just going out.
Let's go!
Vehicular manslaughter!
Oh yeah!
You got fucked up!
I just broke that glass or that ice.
Am I falling on it?
There's so many torches here.
And these rocket boots are...
something.
So good.
It's still day.
But here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to use my special ass potion here.
Three minute duration and press up.
What if we just keep falling?
I'm scared.
I'm fall...
Okay, I'll just fall back it seems.
I'm using the minimap to guide myself right now.
Okay, it looks like that's the end.
I see. Okay, so there is an upper limit there.
That's interesting.
Oh, here we go!
Oh shit!
Like that?
Here we go!
Oh, that... okay.
Weird.
Shoot them out.
Actually, let me grab those things.
They seem relatively rare.
And also...
grab that goldfish.
Bro, I can't hit anything.
Let's keep going.
Two minutes.
Ow!
Make a potion.
Look at this pro movement here.
Isn't that pro?
Okay.
I don't see anything here.
Yeah.
Man, I'm focusing so hard right now.
Eight... 30 seconds.
Here we go!
And it's about to be night.
Oh.
Okay, there's nothing here it seems.
All right, let's go.
Be careful here.
Woo!
Scary.
Time ran out just there.
Meteor head banner.
Hmm.
Okay.
So here's my plan, by the way.
The old man.
This is going to be a crazy boss fight.
Okay, we got to hurry.
I want to use as much of the night as possible.
I have a special plan here.
I think you may know what it is.
But maybe not the intricacies of the plan.
It's something that will only unfold a little later in the plan.
We'll see what I mean.
We're doing the boss fight.
Come on.
Look at them wearing fucking snow covers.
So cute.
The hell?
Oh, it's a star.
Dude, this sky is so far away.
Man!
Mike, what the heck?
I'm really trying to...
Hurry here.
Also, I feel like the night is shorter than the day.
In this game.
Maybe I'm wrong. It just feels that way.
Here we are.
Okay.
Here's the plan.
Oh, this is not even on.
What's this?
Snow coat.
Interesting.
Meteor head shirt, put it.
Now we're going to do the following.
We're going to rub.
And we're going to...
Shoot that thing away.
Drink.
Shoot that fucker.
This one.
And then I will need...
Let's see.
Come on.
I think we're good.
And these monsters are going to be annoying.
Let's just fucking throw some lights here.
We're going to have a rave.
It's raving time.
And then I need this to be on a hotbar.
Or...
Okay.
Strange brew.
Here we go.
Curse you and your people.
Shoot the hands.
Oh, I can't get past his hands.
Here we go.
Okay, not bad.
Okay, so I can actually go through his arms.
It's the hands that are the problem here.
The hands are impenetrable.
Shoot those hands.
Okay, it's time.
No, are you kidding me?
God damn it.
Okay, here's the plan.
The plan was to, as soon as I had my potion on cooldown and I was low,
I was just going to fucking bob up and down in the sky.
And fuck with this guy until I had my potions ready again.
And then I drop back down, do my shit,
and get back into it.
Bro, walking this way every time
is a fucking pain.
What the fuck?
Hold on. I'm going to go back to my house.
Let me just see if I can't craft a goddamn rail.
Because I'm losing my mind.
There's absolutely no way I'm walking that path
every time.
Fuck no.
By the way,
we can utilize the rail against the boss.
Now that I think about it.
So this is maybe great, actually.
I need to...
I think let, I would imagine.
Let's try.
Let's see if he will tell me how to make them.
Let's see here.
Do we have any rails?
Oh, yeah, actually, minecart track.
Requires wood and any iron bar.
That's what I thought.
And would I have?
I have a ton.
There.
Don't... actually, yeah.
Go down here.
There.
Oh, it's 50 at a time.
Whoa, okay. Well, that's...
That's fucking great.
Let's make a thousand.
Let's see how fast this goes.
What?
Oh.
Ah.
Kind of...
Oh, that's annoying.
The trees.
I have an idea.
We're going to make it from the top of the house.
We're going to fucking make a railway
above everything else.
Okay, that's kind of weird.
All right, that sort of works.
Oh, nice. It doesn't fall off.
Look at this shit.
This is like some Walter and Gromit shit.
Is it Wallace and Gromit?
I actually forgot.
Man, it's just barely not enough to...
Wait, that's annoying.
Get that way from me. Yeah.
Oh, no. Hold on.
How am I doing this?
No.
Oh, wait. Is it faster if I spam the button?
Hold on.
No, it's not.
Oh, no, no, no.
Stop!
Jesus!
This is very weird.
Also, how many... Okay, 700 left.
I may not have enough, actually.
Okay, this is how we do it.
Let's go straight.
Wait.
Just find a rhythm here.
Find a good speed.
That seems good.
Ow!
No, not now.
Okay, we got to go up again.
Can you just please go up normally?
For fuck's sake.
Okay.
No, what the fuck?
Bro.
Bruh, bruh, bruh, bruh.
Okay, go.
Go, go, go.
Fuck you, slimes.
Okay, this is a sustainable speed.
Hell, yeah. This is the sweet spot.
Also, we're running out of these things.
We're not going to have enough.
We can go a little faster.
No, we can't.
Man, I thought a thousand would be enough.
Boy, was I wrong.
Oh, dude.
Oh, I have an idea.
We're going to... oh, this is going to be amazing.
I'm going to fucking nail this guy.
I'm going to have a traffic accident at high speed.
That's how I'm going to kill this old man.
Get away from me.
Okay, we're going to need to make more.
The question is, though, can I...
Wait, I can definitely...
Right?
Wait, no, no, no.
Oh, look at that.
There.
Fuck, what do we need to make?
What did we need?
Oh, no. Maybe this one.
If it's not, I guess I can get back quick. Come on.
Yes. Okay, thank God.
Make another thousand. Let's make 1100.
Beautiful.
Oh, yeah, that's nice.
I mean, I guess it would be quick to go back because you can...
I have a fucking railway now.
Let me try this.
That's about the same.
Look, the slime's falling.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Man, this is a long path, huh?
By the time we get there...
Nice.
Okay.
That's how we do that.
Okay, beautiful.
And then, that way, and then it should be smart enough.
Yes, yes, sir.
Thank you.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Dude, I'm gonna be...
Utilizing this railway so hard
when fighting that guy.
Hopefully, his attacks won't knock me off the railway.
That's what I'm afraid of right now.
Okay, we're almost there, actually.
I need to use a different finger to hold down the mouse button.
My pointer finger is getting tired.
I actually have a great idea here.
I'm gonna make a little, uh, funny...
Bend.
When we get there in the road here.
So I can go back and forth.
And just sit on this thing and shoot this shit out of him.
It's gonna be the ultimate drive-by...
Strategy.
Also, hold on, let me see here.
Oh, we're gonna be the perfect height as well.
Look at us.
Ah, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Do not do that.
Don't you, uh, me?
We need to place these again.
Maybe I only need this, actually.
Let's see.
Man, I needed way more than I thought of.
Okay, perfect.
Just make mine hundreds.
Sure.
Here we go.
My fingers.
I tried to double jump. I...
At least we can get back quick because we have a railway.
No.
I tried to double jump so hard and I panicked.
I forgot I had to right-click the goddamn buff.
Shit.
Oh well.
It's okay.
Here we go.
Let's see how fast this goes now.
Ultimate speed.
How fast does it go?
Oh, this.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Look at this.
Just chilling.
Is it getting slower?
Speed up.
Maximum. And this is the plan.
I'm going to sit here.
I'm going to go...
While I'm fighting.
Did I hit something just now?
Fuck, fuck, fuck, all of y'all.
Fuck your trees.
Fuck you.
Ice.
Slimes.
And all that.
Fuck it all.
Okay, we're almost there.
Let's go.
What the?
That was weird.
Let's find the perfect speed again.
This seems right.
Let me just switch fingers.
I'm coming for you, old man.
Slowly but surely.
Get away from me.
Nah.
I don't like that.
It needs to be clean.
Beautiful.
No.
Okay.
I'm starting to get the hang of how to do this quickly.
And here's the thing.
We're going to go like this now.
Like that.
And then we're going to go like that.
And this is the master plan.
I am gonna...
Oh, hold on.
There's gotta be a way to get off this fucking thing.
Without having to right click that.
I need to figure this out.
I need to figure this out, otherwise I'll lose my mind.
Okay, I can use that.
That.
Throw?
Maybe?
Nope.
Stupid slimes.
Right click.
Why is this so hard?
What is wrong with me?
Interact?
Doesn't work.
Jump doesn't work.
Smart cursor auto select left shift?
Quick...
Quick mount.
Is that it?
Oh, fuck yeah.
There it is.
It's a mount.
Look at all the slimes down here, by the way.
I feel like we need to wait for the slimes to go away before we engage the guy.
I need to rebind that shit.
That's a terrible keybinding.
Um...
Mount, put it on...
What do we got?
Maybe...
Do I have anything on E?
Grapple, right.
Mouse 4, maybe.
Oh, oh!
You can even use it to get on.
Oh, perfect.
Okay.
It is happening.
Quick stack.
Okay, here's the plan.
I'm gonna chop down this.
Uh, wait.
Gonna remove a couple of these.
Hop!
Nice.
And then...
We go like this.
Oh, but wait, can I turn?
Ooh, wait a minute now.
Oh, I probably...
I was thinking I could go like this route and then to the right again,
so I can just go back and forth,
but that's probably not gonna work, huh?
But I guess I could do...
Hold on, actually.
Let me try something really fast here.
What if I were to...
Let's say I do something like this.
This is a pure experimentation now.
And then I go like this.
Shit, hold on.
So let's say I go like this here,
and then I jump now, okay?
Get ready.
I jump here.
Hop!
Aha!
Hey, hey, hey!
Right?
Look at this shit.
That's how we do it.
And then...
Oh, I think it's about to be night as well.
That's perfect timing.
Uh, here.
And then we go like this now.
This is gonna be so silly.
Probably unnecessary.
But it's gonna be fun.
So here's the plan.
I can go like this.
Hop!
Why doesn't it register the second time, actually?
Sometimes it doesn't register when I click.
For some reason.
Maybe there's an internal cooldown on it.
If I go like this...
Okay, maybe I just have to time it.
So I jump.
And I keep going.
This way I can be super mobile.
Hell yeah, dude.
So here's a question I have as well.
Will this affect me on the mine card?
Let's see.
I stop.
Let's see here.
So that's the speed there.
Oh my god.
Fuck off, will ya?
So like this?
Okay.
Nah.
Doesn't affect me at all.
So that means I don't need that right now.
I can go with the other one.
What is the other one?
Uh, this one.
Oh wait, did I have this one on?
Nah, doesn't affect me.
Okay.
It's time.
Let's fucking go.
I will engage.
Hyperdrive.
Regeneration.
Swiftness.
Iron skin.
I'm gonna shoot these fools down.
Uh, calming.
Monster lasagna.
And that should be it.
That should be fine.
Here we go.
Excuse me.
Hey!
See ya, bitch!
Yep, that's it.
And then I jump up.
There we are.
I gotta heal.
I gotta get out of here.
Bro, he's super fast.
Hit him!
Shoot him!
Oh, this is terrible.
Oh no.
Go!
Okay, this is not working.
This is not working as I thought it would.
Unfortunately.
Yeah.
God damn it.
I hate this guy!
Okay, this is a terrible strategy.
I take it back.
This is horrible.
Worth a try, though.
God damn it!
You know what?
Maybe I can still make it,
because I have so much speed now.
I can make it back and summon him again.
Let's hurry.
The problem is,
I only have shit bullets now.
Yeah, should have thought about that.
Shark pup.
Also,
I'm gonna go back to my gravitation potion strategy.
Maybe I'll try that from the beginning.
Man, even with...
Okay, actually.
We're soon there.
This is so much faster.
Wait, is that the end of...
No way.
Hold on.
Is that the end of the world?
Wait, he's not here.
You have to wait for the next night.
Oh no.
Alright, I'm exploring to the left, I guess.
Let's see what's over here.
Man, it is dark.
Shit, no, no.
Is this actually the end of the world over here?
The map would suggest it, right?
Yeah, look, we're approaching the sea again.
Shell pile.
Yeah, I think this is
the end of the world.
Obviously, we gotta...
try it.
What is at the end of the world?
What do we got?
That is the end of the world.
Okay, wow.
Interesting.
So, now I reached both sides.
That's honestly kind of nice.
Now I at least know
what to expect from this world and where to go, you know?
Like, it's not infinite in that sense.
That would also be crazy, I guess.
Especially because it's 2D.
Yeah.
Shoot them out of the sky.
I wanna see if there's more of these islands up here.
This potion is insane.
We're slowly exploring everything here.
Kind of satisfying to remove all the dark spots there.
I'll also grab this over here.
I'm focusing so hard when I do this.
I can go way further, actually.
How much time? 40 seconds? Okay.
Ah!
I see something.
Fuck you!
Look at this!
Here we go!
Another bunny constellation.
Swiftness potion, boo.
Lead bar.
Oh, lucky shiny red balloon.
Increases jump height!
Bro, really? How much?
What are we talking here?
I'm intrigued.
Bro, these things have a lot of HP.
Why are there so many?
There we go.
What's that?
Spaghetti bird!
Let's pet it.
Bird.
It's spaghetti!
Dude, this jump increase is...
significant.
Hold on, I need to use this.
Where is it?
There?
Quick stack and also put some shit in there.
Starfish.
Shell pile, go away.
The rope is actually kind of crap, also.
What else?
Okay, so it's day now.
Remove this.
I don't need that right now.
I should just delete it, yeah.
Spaghetti!
Awkward silence.
Feeling petty!
Deliver head pads to the town pet.
Spaghetti!
Bird up.
Okay.
Okay, yeah, I'm liking the minigun.
And it doesn't even have the best bullets.
That's the thing.
I'm taking this with me again.
Oh, it's not empty.
Delete this.
Actually, no, I want to keep this.
Remove this.
Take that Skyware chest.
Spaghetti.
I like spaghetti.
Wait a minute.
Could it be?
I had that same effect at home.
I get it now.
Okay.
Dude, I will use that against the old man.
Bastard!
Nice.
Okay.
All right, Spaghetti.
I'll see you around.
You have an arrow in your head.
This fish is annoying me, actually.
I need to get rid of that.
Nice.
It looks...
Why am I doing this?
Just use that!
What the fuck is wrong with me?
What is actually wrong with me?
I hate the shark bait.
He gets to go away.
Drisken!
Back where I'm from, we only serve root beer.
Okay.
I mean...
I'm going to try one of these, I guess.
Let's try the Explosive Trabrod.
Okay.
Let's see how this works.
I figured.
So, you need...
Cannot be used without Ethereum mana.
And until the Ethereum crystal has been defended.
Probably some event.
Put it in here for now.
And do I want that?
Man, this one right here is...
This one combined with that...
is actually significant.
Look at this.
Not even without the flying.
That's a great amount of height you gain.
So, maybe I can even let go of the rocket boots.
Nah, they're too good, right?
Then again, let's say I don't...
No, I need double jump.
You can't give me double jump and then not use it, you know?
I can't go back to no double jump.
That's just a fact.
I'm going to put this here.
And this one can go...
here. That fits for the gems, right?
Look at all the colors, you know?
This is just for the looks.
I'm not actually going to use them like that.
Okay, let's do some inventory management here.
Put the cloud in there.
We've got gem...
Oh, actually, click on this button.
Lovely.
And summon this.
Take all.
Jesus.
Deposit weapons.
I'm going to put this in there.
This goes in construction.
The sunflowers.
The sunflowers I'm bringing.
I'm bringing those, dude.
Michelinius, let's put this in here.
Um...
Eternia crystal stand.
Interact while carrying an Eternia crystal to summon Etherious portals.
Let's try that.
I didn't buy those for nothing.
Uh...
Let me go on the house.
Eternia crystal rejects this area and pops away instantly.
The tavern keep mention it should rest in a large flat open area.
Oh, okay.
Large flat open area.
I guess this is sort of flat?
This is pretty flat.
Let's try it over here.
Got to get rid of all this.
Ooh, here we go.
Oh, uh...
Old ones army wave one.
Here we go.
Where?
Oh, I just fucking plopped them out of the...
Actually use a...
Where's my other gun?
Ah shit, I don't know what it is.
I'm using this, this is sick.
Sup fools.
You ain't shit, bro.
Easy.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I get it now.
I see.
I see now.
Can I heal it?
Shit.
I mean, I fucked this up already.
This is bad.
Let me put down, do I...
Let me put down...
Oh, I do have this buff.
Use this.
This one is not that great.
Oh, there's...
Oh, no!
They're throwing shit.
Oh, bro, this is this...
Holy shit!
What the fuck!
Okay, see ya.
Oh!
Okay.
Well...
Yeah, this weapon sucks.
It sucks.
I definitely need some better AoE here, man.
Holy shit, that wave was...
Whew!
What do I have?
I can do that better.
Okay, I need to defend it first before you use that.
Okay, gotcha.
Okay.
You know what?
Let me talk to Dante real quick.
Heard a rumor that some clouds are literally out to get you.
Show him who's the boss with one of my guns.
Really?
Flintlock pistol?
You know...
I am curious.
It's very fast...
No, but this one is...
I mean, I gotta try them all.
We're in experimental phase right now.
How does this do?
This kinda seems shit.
Unless it has a special effect.
Extremely weak knockback.
Mmm...
This is a little bit slower, I think.
Yeah, this is faster.
But it's also less damage.
Actually, I have a better undertaker.
What am I doing?
This one.
There we go.
Ah...
Face blades...
I feel like my weapons suck.
I need better weapons.
Like this one is good.
The meatball is kinda good, but...
Not good enough.
Yell.
I just finished my newest creation.
This version doesn't explode violently if you breathe on it too hard.
Okay, that's good. What did you make?
You didn't make anything new.
Allows the combining of some accessories.
So...
I don't understand that fucking thing.
Okay, here's what I'm gonna try.
Potions.
Put all my potions in there for now.
Bait.
What is inside here?
Loot it all.
Do that.
Organics.
Ah, keep this.
You know what, let's have a bunny painting here somewhere.
That's too big!
Oh, we have a room in there.
Next to the bed, that's nice.
No, we don't have...
Oh my god, will you...
There we go.
Get rid of that.
Hey, spaghett!
Plop. Pop.
Splat.
Sure. Sure, sure, buddy.
Whatever.
Put this in here.
Instruction.
In here.
The danger sense potion.
And the lasagna.
Lasagna.
Can go in here.
Weapons in...
Potions in...
Do we have any more potions?
No.
Okay, so here's what I want to do. I want to sort.
Let's put this stuff in here.
Yeah, so now I want to loot all this.
Go around here.
Fuck, I don't understand how this works!
Oh, wait.
No.
Wait.
I need to read this description again.
Nope.
Uh...
Wait, no, no.
Uh, talk to this guy.
Shop.
Allows the combining of some accessories.
How?
How the fuck do you do that?
Hold on a second.
This is an accessory.
Which means all of these are accessories.
So this will allow me to combine them somehow.
How?
Fucking how?
Let me try the weapons.
Let me just take some of those.
Okay.
Let me try...
Deposit.
All?
I'm trying to take all the weapons.
I'm gonna brute force this now.
Wait.
No, wait.
This is just just standard.
Yeah, I can...
Wait.
Do I have...
Oh, I have a keen mace.
But I can make it into a flaming, I guess.
Okay, fine.
Um...
So put all this back.
Maybe it's something to do with the...
You know what? I have an idea.
Maybe this needs to be next to the tinkerer, actually.
It's his workshop, right?
So...
Fucking hell, that thing...
Reminds me of...
The fledging table from Minecraft.
Those that know know.
Oh my god.
Put this one there, I guess.
Okay.
I feel like I need a special weapon to deal with those waves.
I guess the unpleasant meatball is sort of okay,
but the problem is they're coming from both sides.
And I simply don't have the attack speed to deal with both sides at the same time.
You know?
Actually, the mini shark is a material.
Oh yeah, of course it is, because we can make other things.
Let me quickly test something.
Does it say something like...
Mega shark.
Illegal gun parts? Shark fin?
No, I need this. I have no idea where to get that.
So I don't think this is within reach right now.
But there was something else regarding illegal gun parts.
Dante?
You sell this and you sell unholy arrows.
Yeah.
What do you do again?
You sell fucking golfing stuff.
So interesting.
Maybe it's the... oh, wait a minute.
There's an item to reforge.
You know, let me actually try...
Let me try this again.
Hey!
Yo, that's a...
Yo!
Hold on a second.
This is a sick weapon, isn't it?
That's gonna do a shit ton of damage.
Wait a minute now.
Let me try on...
Let's do...
So here's my question.
If I do it on this and that...
I wonder if the chance is the same to get a good item.
What I mean is, this already has 5% speed.
Is it gonna re-roll everything?
Or is it gonna use this as a baseline, right?
I'm gonna try now.
That was significant, man.
Let's see here.
Reforge. Let's try this one first.
One gold.
Agile.
Okay, so this is already better than what I had before.
Let me try this now.
Plus 11, 22.
This one is better.
Yeah, hurtful.
Also, look how this one is green.
I think this one is really good because it's red.
And look at all the modifiers it has.
Okay, so it's like it's a bit of a gamble because you spent some money and...
You're not sure where you're gonna get, right?
So yeah, I don't know how if I want to spend all that money.
This seems like a quick way to use all the money, right?
In fact, there's something I want to try.
I do have an extra...
thingy.
Where is it? Is it up here?
This one.
Shield of Kittullu.
I need to see exactly what I can use that for.
Kittullu.
Oh wait, I can't even use that. Never mind.
Which one was it? There was something I could use.
Was it a weapon? Hold on.
This is a material.
Okay, let me actually try this. And let me try...
This one, actually.
And...
I could use this one. This one is actually also...
possible.
Okay, let's try this.
Remind me more... Oh yeah, this is the crazy weapon
that requires all of these.
Yeah, I remember this.
And this one...
Crystal Shard. I don't think I have any of those.
But this is a very good weapon, holy shit.
What about this? Enchanted Boomerang?
Requires a Fallen Star!
Hey, I can do that!
Oh, but wait...
Let's try that, actually.
I have one.
What do I need for that?
Boomerang... I need...
Nothing. Okay.
You can do it right now.
Okay, so that one didn't get any modifiers.
It's just baseline.
Okay.
Cool.
Put it back in, I guess.
And now let me try this.
So there's this one.
There's this one.
There's...
What should I try?
Actually, the Bucknet.
Can also be tried, I guess.
This one can create something nice later on.
Radar.
See, why do I have two of these? I should just get rid of one.
Okay.
Dylan. And Dylan, no.
What about the radar?
Rec 3000.
Telecounter.
Just place how many monsters have been killed.
Wait a minute.
Oh, no, I don't have that.
What can I make from this?
Man of Regeneration. Charm of Myths.
Provides life regeneration and reduces the cooldown of healing potions by 25%.
Okay.
This is on two.
Yoyo Bag.
Gives the user Master Yoyo Skills.
Wide String.
What does that even do, though?
What does Master Yoyo Skills even mean?
Magic Cuffs.
Man of Regeneration Band.
Oh, this actually requires the Tinkerose Workshop.
Hold on a second.
So maybe I did do it right.
I just didn't have the combinations, then.
There's no way.
I had so many, though.
Wait a minute.
Loot all these.
Hold on now.
Let me check up here.
Yeah, look.
None of these go together.
I think I did it right.
I just didn't have anything that was actually compatible.
Jesus Christ.
I guess that's super unlucky, then.
Why are there goldfish here?
Where's my thing?
It's somewhere.
Okay.
We're closer to solving this whole mystery here.
Put all this back.
And give me my...
Where's my damn net?
Oh, God.
Where did I put it?
Oh, wait. Is it in my...
Fuck!
There.
Okay, there's nothing in there.
Wait, what?
Ah, here it is.
Wood platform.
This.
No.
This one.
Okay.
Hey, Ohano!
Would you be interested in these?
Thank you.
Now put in this.
Okay.
Is it about to be...
Oh shit, did I just do this throughout the whole night?
Or is it just becoming day?
I need to figure out how to make that stupid clock.
I'm gonna do it now, actually, before I forget.
Take all.
Can we make a clock?
Maybe over here.
Dylan!
Uh, silver, maybe?
Silver watch.
Chain.
Ah, there it is.
Okay.
Chain.
But I guess it's morning now, so, okay.
I'm gonna make a silver watch.
What do I need to make it, though?
Table...
And chair.
Okay.
Interesting.
Does this count milliseconds and this only counts seconds or what?
I mean, I gotta get a platinum watch.
Platinum watch.
Yeah, dude.
Tells the time.
Let's put this in here.
Utility outfit.
Can we switch?
Oh, switch.
720, ah, nice.
Finally.
Look at this, we get all the information here with this loadout.
Beautiful.
Oops.
Okay.
Um...
Man, I need to...
You know what, actually?
I just had a great idea for the waves.
How about I just make a shit ton of bombs?
Oh, wait, no, that's gonna destroy the ground.
That's not good.
That's bad.
I don't like that.
But it wasn't an idea, though.
That's some AOE.
Put all these back.
Is there really...
Hold on, maybe I...
What does that do?
Oh, my God!
Fucking hell!
Okay, so there is actually a way to do it.
But the game doesn't tell you, it seems.
So if I all click on it, it actually locks it.
If I control click it, it puts it in trash.
Fucking fantastic.
That's what I needed so bad.
God damn.
Okay, so this stays, this stays.
And man, that just made me so happy.
This one also stays.
But I can still use it, right?
And put it...
Oh, it's even gonna...
And if I put it...
The item is locked itself.
Beautiful.
Sort.
Locked this as well.
Oh, that's so good.
So happy.
The rest looks nice.
This one doesn't have to be here, I guess.
Okay.
Okay, let's see.
I actually miss...
I'm missing one.
Let me put this back.
I don't think I want to use the mini shark.
I do want to make better bullets,
because these suck.
You know what, Dylan? Help me.
Yeah, fuck your stylist.
A lot of people have moved in lately, haven't they?
Party girl was surely moving.
Wondering merchant.
Some of them sell merchandise, gotcha.
Wait till you see reigning slime.
I've seen it.
Beautiful lanterns.
Seen it.
Please, empty...
Yep.
Okay.
Marble...
Mar...
Wait, marble bio.
I wonder if that's that area I saw in the cave that looked...
odd.
Maybe that's a marble bio.
In granite biomes, the very stone itself is a threat.
Frequently coming to life and attacking intruders.
Yeah, I've seen that.
While you explore the underground,
you may occasionally encounter helpful fairies.
Yeah, I haven't seen one in a while.
Old dungeon not far from here.
Now would be a good time to go check it out.
Are you perchance talking about the one with the old man?
Normally I try to teach you all about the old one's army,
but you should probably ask Driskin about that.
Yeah, I've asked him already.
Let's see here.
Obsidian form when water and lava...
Oh, that sounds very Minecrafty.
It can be used to protect against intense heat.
Oh.
Speaking of traveling merchants...
Mercer!
Let's see more.
He really has no appreciation for a really good deal.
Oh yeah.
What's...
Wait, it might be broken?
Hmm.
Uses mana.
Demon horns.
Bro, I think I'm gonna buy that.
Thank you.
Let me see.
Oh, that's a lot.
Oh, that's very slow.
Yo, the mana regen is...
nuts.
What the fuck?
Bro...
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Speaking of sniper rifles,
I finally got my own.
And if this is a laser, will it go through enemies?
Bro, I need to...
I need to...
I need to test this immediately.
Onward, snowball steeds.
On to combat.
Let's see.
Red regen here.
Let's see here.
Oh, it bounces.
Wait, it totally...
Wait, what?
Wait, there's a chance for it to penetrate?
Is that what I'm seeing?
It might be broken.
Is that what that's supposed to mean?
I don't know why that's so funny to me.
This is awesome.
Oh, it actually uses a lot of mana.
That's when the mana potion comes in, dude.
I don't have it on me right.
Actually, I do.
Actually, I don't.
Never mind.
Oh, it totally goes through!
But...
stuff.
Yeah, it's definitely broken, bro.
Oh, they... wait.
Okay.
So, enemies drop mana when you...
When you have a mana weapon and you kill them with it.
That's actually kind of interesting.
Let me go back.
I want to try something.
I want to repair this bastard.
Fjall!
No, wait.
No, wait. Yeah, fjall.
Fjall? Fjall.
Fjall!
Try this one.
Seven gold, though.
You made it annoying?
Mystic.
Damn.
It's still broken, though.
But it's better now.
Let me see if it still does that thing.
14 mana.
Oh, minus 12 was a mana cost. That's actually nice.
But, I mean, mana regenerates so fast.
Look at this. I shoot.
Immediately full mana.
It's really no problem at all.
Holy shit.
That's really nice.
In fact, it's so nice
that I'm going to go try this thing again over here.
Where did I leave those?
Oh, this is going to be a problem.
Here?
Shit.
In here?
That...
Oh, this is going to be painful.
Where the hell did I leave those?
Where's that little crystal?
Is it here?
Crystal?
It's a tiny crystal.
Crystal.
Tiny...
Tiny, tiny icon.
It's not in here.
I mean, I guess I can just buy a new one.
Also, I should buff myself up before I try that again.
Probably smart.
I have no idea where the fuck I left that.
That's unreal.
Alright.
That thing is fucking gone.
Drisken.
I do need myself another one of these.
Oh, it doesn't cost very much either.
Maybe it got consumed when I used it actually.
It does say consumable.
I just seem to remember when it was finished that I still had this in my inventory.
That's why I'm so confused here.
Yes.
Now I grab my potions.
This one.
No, I'm saving that.
One of these.
Let's go...
Man, actually.
So wait, how do I...
Is there a keybind for just that then?
I need to check that out.
Immunity to lava.
Let's see here.
Quick mana.
J.
That needs to be changed immediately.
Let's put that on...
This one.
In backslash, sure.
Okay.
We try again.
Mercer has departed, that's fine.
Here we go!
Now I'm gonna stand here and wait.
I need to zoom out a bit.
Oh yeah, baby!
Oh!
Brother!
Oh, this is fantastic!
It's actually so great that I...
Why can't...
Okay, never mind.
For some reason I can't place any blocks right now.
It's super weird.
And then we try this mana potion.
It works like you would expect.
In fact, I may kill these when they're close, so they drop the mana close to me.
This is the galaxy brain move.
See? The mana is there, ready to be taken when I need it.
Bring on the next wave!
Why can't I place the block?
Bro, this thing is insane.
Yeah, I'm running out of mana here.
Let's wait a bit.
In fact, I can switch to my other weapon while I wait.
Let's grab this mana here.
This is working wonders.
Not bad!
In fact, I'm saving my mega laser thingy.
For when things get really tough.
Oops, nope.
Oh my god, there's so many.
This is actually getting a little...
This is getting a little bad.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Oh, they're shooting shit at me now.
Oh no, this is actually bad!
Oh, I can't, I can't survive this.
Oh my god.
Bro!
Holy shit!
No, they're destroying the thingy!
Also, I should have a statue here.
I don't know why I'm not using that.
Fallen Star.
I can't place anything for some reason.
Uh-oh, we got flying dudes.
Oh man.
I'm so dead.
There's no way I can do this.
Absolutely not.
Not strong enough.
So weird that, like, hold on.
Yeah, I figured it was because of the thing happening,
but it doesn't make any fucking sense that I can't do that.
Literally every other fucking thing in this game
allows me to place it during any kind of fight, right?
Suddenly I can. It makes no fucking sense.
I was so confused. Look at this, I can do it now,
but I couldn't do it before.
Man, look at all that mana.
That mana though.
Not that I need it.
Okay, I'm gonna put my stuff back in the bag.
Chain.
Goes in here.
Sunflower. I kinda wanna bring that with me.
I'm not sure if this is good.
Actually, if it hits a bunch of enemies,
if this armor penetration works on every single enemy it penetrates,
like, let's say the laser goes through 10 enemies,
if this armor penetration works on all of those,
that could be big.
Right?
So I'm gonna put that in here.
And get ready to use that next time I do that.
Wait a minute.
Why is the 2 up here changing size when I grab this?
It probably just means I can't use it while I have it in my hand.
The evidence shall be deleted of what took place here.
None shall ever know.
Actually, I'll delete it entirely.
Okay.
This is a great weapon.
I can't wait to use this on the old man.
The Mystic Gray Sabinator.
Yeah.
Gimme this.
And you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm actually gonna take my...
Minigun.
Oh, hold on.
Hey!
How dare you.
Get out of here.
Wait, did I produce a graveyard over there?
I'm gonna take this.
I'm actually gonna make it into the star weapon.
Because that sounds insane.
Requires meteorite bars? I have that.
Oh yeah.
And what exactly...
What station do I need for this?
Just an animal. Okay.
Gotcha.
Oh, did I need more fallen stars maybe?
Star cannon.
Five of them. Okay.
66.
If that's gonna go grrrrr and use stars like that,
let's test.
Let's have that here so I can see the ammo.
Oh my god.
Okay.
The question is though...
Okay, I can't pick the ammo back up.
I was wondering maybe that would be the case. Holy shit.
You know what?
This is gonna be the ultimate...
boss killer, dude.
Yep.
That's gonna be a lot of damage.
But it costs a lot of stars.
I guess I can start collecting them, huh?
Let me put them in here actually.
In the star box.
Actually, it kinda looks...
Yeah, that looks like a star.
Let's put these in here.
Oh, I'm so glad I discovered this fucking mechanic here.
That makes me so happy.
Mechanic can go in here for now.
Sort these.
This one is also super good now.
I feel like I have a good selection of...
weapons now.
This annoying tungsten hammer...
has been annoying for the longest time.
So annoying.
Such an annoying hammer.
Actually, let's just keep it...
in the inventory like this.
Because whenever I need a hammer,
I just shift click, right?
That's fine.
Potions...
in there.
And now I'm ready...
to end it here.
This is a good place to start.
Uh, stop.
And I'm gonna kill that old piece of shit next time.
Hell yeah.
Oh my god, it's actually...
How long did I go for?
Four hours. I was planning on three.
Damn it.
Why is this game so...
It just takes time.
Like, it completely...
steals your time.
Hahaha.
Oh man.
I need to...
Hold on.
Yeah.
How's everybody doing?
I don't know why the chat is doing that when I switch scene.
It's an odd thing.
Nice!
You see the new emote.
Crowwater made that one.
Got a set and alarm. Actually, that's a great idea.
Yeah.
Set a timer. Definitely.
Oh yeah, I have a watch now.
That's true.
Definitely.
Um...
Yeah.
I'm gonna do that next time. That's a great idea.
I don't know why I didn't think of that.
Everyone was happy when you figured out the tinkerer table.
That's good. I was too.
Well, I feel like I always knew...
sort of knew how it worked,
but I just couldn't believe
that I didn't have any combinations.
That's the thing I didn't understand.
Like, I was pretty sure it just worked like any of the other ones.
Right?
But it was just like I had so many accessories
that it was almost unbelievable
that none of them would go together.
Yeah, over a great stream like always.
You have to read more carefully. People are going insane in chat.
That's okay. I mean, you can go insane. That's okay.
Here's the thing though. I'm just sitting here playing my game, man.
And...
I know people get upset by certain things,
but that's how it is when you play a game blind like this.
It's just... it's gonna make people upset, I guess.
But that's just how it is.
It's not bothering me.
I'm having fun, you know?
As long as I'm having fun, then...
then it's good.
I mean, here's a pro tip though.
If there's very frustrating parts,
I suggest just waiting for the vaude
and just skip through those, you know?
Watch the good parts.
Or something.
Terraria veterans are the most ferocious.
It just takes us over and makes us monsters.
Yeah, you become demons.
Demonic people.
But that's okay. I mean, I completely get it.
This is an older game by now, right?
So, just like Minecraft, there are so many...
parts to this game.
So many aspects that people have gotten used to
throughout the years, I guess.
Just like Minecraft, right?
And to people, it's common nature how this game works.
But this game works in very mysterious ways.
I can tell you that as someone who has never played this.
There are some very obscure mechanics in this game.
So demon!
That's so demon!
I personally love the chat going crazy.
I mean, people have been saying this
ever since the first time I started streaming it, right?
People always go crazy in the chat.
It's part of it.
I gotta say, though, this game is difficult.
It's a surprisingly difficult game.
I expected this to be a little less difficult.
Rainworld, on the other hand, I sort of expected it to be difficult.
But this one, I was like, ah, Terraria, it's like...
Minecraft, but in 2D, you know, it can't be worse than...
I will say it's harder than Minecraft.
For sure.
This chat was suffering exquisitely.
Amazing.
I am so sorry to everyone who's suffering.
But you have to remember, I'm having a ton of fun with this.
So...
I mean, imagine if we both were suffering.
If I were suffering and you, that would be horrible.
But at least one of us is enjoying it.
Manton, or Manton?
Are you Danish?
I feel like we're Swedish or Norwegian or something.
You motivated me to play Terraria again.
So I've been playing while watching stream.
It's been fun to compare our rate of progress.
When you say compare rate of progress,
you mean you're almost done with the game, right?
And I'm just sitting here trying to get started.
Printing those rails.
Man, I laid down some rails today.
And that's the good part.
Whenever it's gonna be night, I can immediately go to the old man.
I look forward to that, actually.
And now that I have a watch,
I go inside a mine, right?
I mine a lot of shit, I explore.
And then when time hits midnight,
I teleport back home and I instantly jump on the minecart
and I go straight to the old man.
And then I ram him with the minecart.
But I gotta say, this game is really fun so far.
I'm having fun with this man.
This is a very unique game.
I was very surprised to find the edge of the world to the left being there.
Like the world is surprisingly compact.
So I guess that means all the stuff is happening down below.
So I'm gonna have to go exploring, you know?
Can't wait for that.
As long as you're having fun, I couldn't care less if you miss out on certain stuff.
I mean, I'll certainly miss out on certain things.
Definitely.
I mean, that's just guaranteed.
I am gonna miss things. Probably big things as well.
And that's just how it is.
On a second playthrough though, this game I feel like would be really fun to try again from the beginning.
It's one of those games that I think has good replay value.
You know, since you know all this information now, you can get some nice gear from the get-go
and since I know how the combat works and all that, it could be really fun.
I did pick a medium-sized world. That's true.
Quote of the stream. Oh no, it's masturbating.
Like, I said that out loud and immediately like, oh yeah, that sounds like that.
But then I thought it was funny.
Is there an unofficial Terraria server yet? Is that actually a thing?
Can you have like a server with like a lot of people just like Minecraft?
I know you can play with friends in this like co-op, but an actual dedicated server?
Is that a thing? How would that even work?
People have thousands of hours. This game is very replayable. Yeah, that's what I thought.
That's what I thought.
I found the catfish though.
Not the bonnie fish, but you know, catfish will have to do.
That made me happy.
Oliver, you didn't do a single Terraria Hurt Soundground today. Is that true?
There's no way that's true.
I feel like I did.
I must have.
Congratulations on getting catfished.
Thanks.
Thanks, Bailey, that's great.
In my opinion, the game is better playing singleplayer.
That's fair.
I tend to agree with that most with most games as well.
I like the singleplayer experience except competitive games such as Starcraft.
By definition, that one is like, I mean, singleplayer is also cool in that, like the campaign.
But for me, it's all about the latter, you know.
I like how much you hate the brat. I mean, don't you?
He's an asshole and I didn't do anything to him and he's treating me like garbage.
How long do you estimate it will take for you to complete this game?
Guest?
I actually have no clue.
I feel like I am pretty far, but I could be wrong.
Don't confirm or deny that.
But I'm also ready to accept that I'm not far at all.
So, you know.
I love the spaghetti.
Did you get that reference though?
Hunter.
Do you know where that is from?
How far do you think you are? I don't know.
Maybe...
I want to say...
Since I always overestimate, I'm gonna say 30%.
I'm gonna lowball it.
30%, but don't deny or confirm.
The funny touch must forget.
True Terraria player killing bunnies without remorse and hating the angler.
Is that a common theme?
I guess everyone would hate the angler.
Why would you love him, right?
I don't know, maybe he has a character arc.
Maybe he has a change of heart later on.
And he becomes nice.
I would like that.
People are like, interesting.
How many tries do you anticipate for...
Skeletron?
Oh, you mean like the old man?
Probably a lot.
I feel like he's very difficult.
But then again, I feel like as soon as I...
If I get his hands, I think it will turn into an easier boss fight.
Not an easy one, but an easier.
So we'll see.
And now that I have the laser pew pew,
hopefully that can help me.
All my homies hate the angler.
We would all like if the angler stopped me.
And the thing is, the angler...
Someone who goes fishing and stuff...
I feel like you always expect that person to be like super sweet.
And calm and caring, right?
And then we have this little kid.
Just being an asshole.
It goes against everything.
I'm not okay with that.
Anyway.
Oh man, I think it's time for me to head out of here.
It's 11 o'clock here.
So I'm gonna do that.
Guys, thanks for watching.
I'm having a blast with this game.
I know it may be slow.
I know it may be frustrating at times.
But all things in good time.
I'll make it through this.
I mean, I'll play it as long as it's fun.
And so far, it's a hell of a time.
So thanks for watching.
And I'll see you in the next...
Goodbye.